--==本影片由 CMCT 团队 荣誉出品==--
更多精彩影视 请访问 http://cmct.cc
影片压制:墨小魚  字幕调校:墨小魚  招募Q号:76846146
靠
Oh fuck.
『杯酒人生』
- 怎么了? - 迈尔斯 你能不能挪一下你的车 拜托?
- Uh yeah? - Miles can you move your car please?
- 为什么? - 因为修屋顶工人的卡车要进来
- Why? - Because the roofers gotta get the truck in.
- 你车停的不太对好么? - 好行
- You didn't park too good. Okay? - Yeah. All right.
等一下
Hold on.
(星期六)
(海景公寓)
(加州圣地亚哥)
抱歉 抱歉 先生们
Sorry. Sorry gentlemen.
对不起
Sorry.
哦 靠!
Oh fuck me!
我知道我说过会在中午前到那儿
I know I saidI would be there by noon...
但是我的楼在翻修有一大堆的事
but uh there's all of this workgoing on at my building...
简直就是场噩梦
and it's just a total nightmare.
我有些事今天早上必须处理
I had a bunch of stuffI had to deal with this morning...
不过 我已经上路了
but I'm on my way.
我现在就出门了
I'm out the door right now.
嗨 西蒙 嗨 迈尔斯
- Hi Simon. - Hey Miles.
- 三倍浓缩咖啡 - 在这里喝么?
- Triple espresso please? - For here?
呃 不我已经晚了 给我打包吧
Uh no actually.I'm running late. Make it to go.
再给我一份纽约时报和一个菠菜牛角面包
And give me a New York Timesand a spinach croissant.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 啊! - 嗯 你好
- Ah! - Well hello!
- 你好 Erganian夫人最近好么? - 进来吧
- Hello Mrs. Erganian. How are you? - Come on in.
- 谢谢杰克还在这里么? - 是的
- Thank you. Is Jack still here? - Yes.
看看猫给拽的
Look what the cat dragged.
- 嗨 大家好抱歉啊 - 嗨
- Hi everybody. Sorry. - Hey.
某人终于来了
Somebody finally arrived.
你终于到了飞毛腿先生
You finally got here. Mr. Prompt.
- 哦 记不记得我的孩子们? Alex Helen? - 嗨 你们好
- Oh remember my kids? Alex Helen? - Hi. How are you?
我们还在想你是不是走错了路 跑到墨西哥的提哇纳去了…
We were thinking maybe you wentthe wrong way you went to Tijuana...
- 对 - 然后他们不放你回来
- Right. - and they don't let you back.
- 是啊 是啊! - 爸爸!
- Yes! Yes! - Daddy!
- 我不得不行贿他们 - 嗨 迈尔斯
- I had to bribe them. - Hey Miles.
嗨 你好 克莉丝汀
Hey. How are you Christine?
高速公路塞的让人难以置信
Yeah the freeway was unbelievable.
真是难以置信 一路上车挤车的
Unbelievable.It was bumper - to - bumper the whole way.
我想大家周末出门都比较早
People getting an early starton the weekend I guess.
所以我就晚点出来 可还是…
Granted I got a late start but...
好了 我们都很高兴你能来
Well we're just glad you made it.
克莉丝汀 你为什么不问问迈尔斯关于蛋糕的事?
Christine why don't youask Miles about the cake?
- 好主意跟我来 - 怎么回事?
- Oh good idea. Come with me. - What's this?
我们可能没时间了 我们马上得出发了
We don't really have time for that 'cause we gotta hit the road.
- 哦 来吧 就一秒钟的事 - 就是
- [Christine] Oh come on.!It's just gonna take a second.! - Yeah.
嗯
[Miles] Mmm.
杰克告诉我们说你正在出版一本书祝贺你
Jack tells us you are publishing a book.Congratulations.
- 呃… - 是啊 祝贺你
- Uh... Yes congratulations.
是的 不过 呃确切的说还没有敲定呢
Yes well uh it's not exactly finalized yet.
- 就是有人表示感兴趣 而且… - 你的朋友很谦虚
- So... There has been some interest and... Your friend is modest.
得了 来吧 迈尔斯 别那么谦虚了 满足一下他们吧
Oh come on Miles.Don't be so modest. Indulge them.
- 别让我当个撒谎的人啊 - 你的书是关于什么主题的?
- Don't make me out to be a liar. - What is the subject of your book?
- 纪实的? - 呃 不 是…是小说
- Nonfiction? - Uh no. It's... It's a novel.
- 虚构的对 - 哦
- Fiction. Yes. - Oh.
不过有很多部分取材于我自己的生活…
Although there is quite a bitfrom my own life...
所以我想 从技术上讲 算部分纪实吧
so I suppose that technically some of it is nonfiction.
好 我喜欢纪实的
Good. I like nonfiction.
这个世界有太多我们需要了解的
There is so much to knowabout this world.
我觉得读那些别人编造出来的东西简直是浪费时间
I think you read something somebodyjust invented it waste of time.
这个观点很有意思
That's an interesting perspective.
- 那 你比较喜欢哪一个? - 呃 两个都喜欢
- So which one do you like better? - Oh well I like them both.
不过 呒 如果非要选的话 我得说我更喜欢那个黑的
But um if pressed I would have to saythat I prefer the dark.
给你说过了!
- [Murmuring] - [Jack] Told ya.!
- 再见 - 再见
- Bye - bye. - Bye.
- Bye. - Bye.
再见
Bye.
你他妈的刚才在哪儿? 嗯? 我在那儿都快死了
Where the fuck were you man? Huh?I was dying in there.
- 本来我们现在都应该在100英里开外了 - 交通堵塞 我也没办法
- We're supposed to bea hundred miles away by now. - I can't help the traffic.
哦 得了吧 你他妈的酒鬼你自己明白
Oh come on. You're fucking hungover.You know you are.
好吧 我昨天晚上是尝了一点 没错
Okay there wasa tasting last night yes.
我不过是想给我们的车旅准备点好东西看那个盒子
But I wanted to get us something nicefor the ride up. Check out the box.
你干吗告诉他们我的小说已经在出版了?
Why did you tell themthat my novel was being published?
- 因为你说过你都联系好了 - 没有 我没说过 没有
- 'Cause you said you had it all lined up. - No I didn't. No. No.
我说的是"迷题"出版社的人表示有兴趣
What I said was that there wassome interest at Conundrum.
- 对"迷题" - 那个编辑要把小说递给高层编辑
- Yeah. Conundrum. - And that one of the editorswas passing it to a senior editor.
我觉得听上去不错听上去你已经搞定了
Sounds pretty good to me.Sounds like you're in.
没有 希望并不大
No. It's a long shot.
再说 "迷题"只是一家小的专业出版社
Besides Conundrum it's just a small specialty press.
我不打算抱太大希望
I'm not gonna get my hopes up.
你知道 我已经不再关心这事了
You know? I've stopped caring.
算了吧我已经不再关心了
The hell with it.I have stopped caring.
听起来好像这次能成我是说 我能感觉到
It sounds like it's gonna happen this time.I mean I can feel it.
我想就是这次了嗯?
I think this is the one. Huh?
我真为你感到骄傲 伙计
I'm really proud of you man.
- 现在别打开还热着呢 - 为什么不行?
- Don't open that now. It's warm. - Why not?
杰克 这可是1992年的Byron酒这可是非常稀罕的懂么?
Jack that is a 1992 Byron.It's really rare. Okay?
- 我一直存着它别打开… - 好的 我不打开
- I've been saving it. Don't... All right. I won't open it.
杰克
Jack!
浪费了一半
- [Chuckling] - Half of it gone.
嗨 闭嘴行不行!
Hey shut up. Okay?
祝我们度过愉快地一周!
Here's to a great week.
来吧
- Come on. - [Champagne Pouring]
嗯 绝对
Yes. Absolutely.
虽然你很蠢…
Despite your crass behavior...
我还是很高兴我们这次能一起来
I'm actually gladwe're getting this time together.
对我也这样想
Yeah. Me too.
我期待这一天已经很久了
I've been looking forward to thisfor a long time.
- 我还以为这一天永远也不会来呢 - 哎呀 味道真不错!
- Was beginning to thinkit was never gonna happen. - Man! That's tasty!
百分之百加州黑皮诺(pinot noir)葡萄单一品种的葡萄园
That's 1 00% pinot noir.Single vineyard.
他们现在都不造这种酒了
They don't even make it anymore.
- 黑皮诺葡萄? - 嗯
- Pinot noir? - Mm - hmm.
- 那怎么这是白色的? - 哦 上帝啊
- Then how come it's white? - Oh Jesus.
可别在葡萄酒园问这样的问题
Don't ask questions like thatup in wine country.
- 他们会以为你是弱智呢 - 告诉我么
- They'll think you're some kind of dumbshit. - Just tell me.
红葡萄酒的颜色来自葡萄皮
Color in red winescomes from the skins.
这个酒的葡萄汁不一样 是自然流出的 不是挤压的…
This juice on the other hand is free run...
所以在发酵的时候不会接触到葡萄皮…
so that there's no skin contactduring fermentation...
对了 你有没有看过我最近的草稿?
[Miles] Did you read the latest draft by the way?
- 嗯 看过了 看过了 - 觉得怎样?
- [Jack] Oh yeah.yeah. - And?
非常棒
It's great.
我是说 有很多出改动结构更加紧凑了
I mean there are so many improvements.It's much tighter.
就是看上去…不知道 好像更凝固了似的
Just seems... I don't know more congealed or something.
呒新的结局怎么样? 你喜不喜欢?
Mm - hmm. What about the new ending?Did you like that?
哦 对 新结局比老的那个结局好太多了
Oh yeah. New endingvastly superior to the old ending.
就根本没有新结局
There is no new ending.
从750页以后就没有改动
Page 7 50 on is exactly the same.
噢 那大概是看着象新的吧…
Well maybe it just seemed new...
难道是因为所有导致结局的情节都变了?
because everything leading up to itwas so different?
对!肯定是这个原因!
Yeah! That must be it!
哇我们为什么要下车?
Whoa. Why are we getting off?
- 呃 我想停一下 - 干什么?
- Uh I just wanna make one quick stop. - For what?
- 我想我们可以去和我妈妈打个招呼 - 你妈妈?
- I just thought we could saya quick hello to my mother. - Your mother?
看 明天是她生日好么?
Look it's her birthday tomorrow.Okay?
- 我觉得路过不进去拜访挺不对的 - 好吧
- And I don't feel right driving byand not stopping in. - Okay.
- 马上就好她就住在高速公路边上 - 好吧!
- It'll take a second.She's right off the freeway. - Okay.!
我不知道是她生日她今年多大年纪了?
I didn't know it was her birthday.How old is she gonna be?
呃 嗯…70…多吧
Uh oh... 70 - something.
噢 这个 帮我那一下
Oh. Here hold thesefor just a second.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 惊喜! - 惊喜!
- Surprise.! - Surprise!
- 生日快乐 妈妈! - 生日快乐!
- Happy birthday Mom! - Happy birthday!
哦 上帝啊!迈尔斯!杰克!
Oh my God! Miles! And Jack!
真是个惊喜!
What a surprise!
我都不记得上次你给我带花是什么时候了!
I can't remember the last timeyou brought me flowers!
生日快乐 妈妈
Happy birthday Mom.
花是我们俩共同送的
They're from both of us. [Chuckling]
- 一个著名的演员给我的生日献花? - 是么? 是的!
- A famous actorbringing me flowers for my birthday! - Right? Yeah!
- 我感到非常特别 - 还有香槟!
- Don't I feel special? - [Jack] And champagne.!
- 这个著名的演员下周要结婚了 妈妈 - 噢 对了
- Famous actor's getting married next week Mom. - Oh that's right!
真是太好了
Isn't that nice.
我希望那个女孩能知道自己有多幸运…
I hope that girl knowshow lucky she is...
嫁给了一个像德里克·索墨斯比一样的人
marrying no lessthan Derek Sommersby.
天哪 那是大概11年前了吧 雷蒙德太太
Gosh that was like 1 1 years ago Mrs. Raymond.
反正 你在那个电视剧里特别棒!
- Well you were wonderful in that show.! - [Laughs]
那个剧没让你成为世界上最红的影星真是罪过!
Why that didn't make you the biggestmovie star in the world is a sin!
哦 现在 迈尔斯…
Oh now Miles...
为什么不告诉我你来是给我带来这个英俊的男人?
why didn't you tell me you were comingand bringing this handsome man?
看我打扮得多好!
Look how I'm dressed!
我得快点去化化妆
I've gotta run and put my face on.
你看上去很美 雷蒙德太太
You look fabulous Mrs. Raymond.
哦 别这样!
Oh stop it!
你们随便点
- Make yourselves comfortable. - [TV:Announcer Faint]
- 你们饿不饿? - 嗯 我饿了
- You boys hungry? - Yeah I'm hungry.
[电视播音员：随着战争伤亡人数…]
[TV:Announcer Continues] Along with the battle casualties...
一点零食就可以了
Just a snack.
[德国损失了一百万人]
the Germans lost almost a million men.
[为了补充人员希特勒不得不转向最后的人力来源]
To replace them Hitler turnedto his last resort of manpower.
这真好吃 雷蒙德太太绝对好吃
This is delicious Mrs. Raymond.Absolutely delicious.
- 唔 - 只是剩下的而已
- Mmm. - They're just leftovers.
呃 这是鸡肉么?
[Chuckles] I - Is this chicken?
我本来可以做些更花哨的吃的…
I could have made something fancier...
如果某人让我事先知道某人…
if a certain someone had let me knowthat a certain someone...
要来拜访而且要带一个特殊的朋友
was coming for a visitand bringing a certain special friend.
这是一个惊喜 妈妈
It was a surprise Mom.
而且我还可以换上干净的床单
And I could've already put clean sheets...
铺在另外那张床上和折叠床上
on the other bed and the foldout.
你们留下吧
You are staying.
温迪·罗恩和双胞胎11：30来接我们去喜来登吃早午餐
Wendy Ron and the twins are picking us upat 1 1 :30 to go to brunch at the Sheraton.
他们在那有一份极好的工作
They do a magnificent job there.
- 你和温迪讲了? - 就刚才
- You talked to Wendy? - Just now.
她高兴极了!双胞胎们…
She's thrilled! And the twins...
不 不 不要了我肯定不要
No no I bet. I bet. Yeah.
那 你看 杰克很想…呃…去 唔…
Well you know Jack is pretty eagerto uh to get up to um...
你知道的
[Stammering] You know.
呃 不过 对 当然我们看看怎么样
Uh but yeah absolutely.We'll see how it goes.
那好吧 你俩想怎样就怎样吧
Well you boys do what you want.
我只是觉得在我生日的时候 我们能像一家人那样聚在一起挺好的
I just thought it would be nice for usto be together as a family on my birthday.
唔唔
Mm - hmm. Mm - hmm.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
你拍的另外那个叫什么来着?
And what was that other one you did?
就是你演一个慢跑的人
The one where you were the jogger.
哦 那个是 呃 Spray 'n Wash清洁剂广告
Oh that was for um Spray 'n Wash.
Spray 'n Wash!就是这个!
Spray 'n Wash! That's the one!
天哪我记得那个和我一起拍这个的女孩 她可真是个尤物
Gosh. I remember the girl that wasin it with me. She was somethin'.
我就记得你慢跑来着
[Mrs. Raymond] I just remember you jogging.
呜噢!
[Jack Laughing] Whoo - hoo!
那 婚礼什么时候?
[Mrs. Raymond] So when's the wedding?
下周六 妈妈不记得了? 我们告诉过你的
Next Saturday Mom.Remember? We told you.
迈尔斯是我的伴郎 雷蒙德太太我最重要的人
And Miles is my best man Mrs. Raymond.My main man.
迈尔斯 你什么时候再结婚啊?
Miles when are you goingto get married again?
我刚刚离婚 菲利斯
I just got divorced Phyllis.
已经两年了 伙计
[Jack] Two years ago buddy.
你应该跟她和好…
You should get back together...
跟维多利亚
with Victoria.
她对你很合适
She was good for you.
她对你很合适!
She was good for you!
而且那么漂亮 那么聪明
And so beautiful and so intelligent.
你认识她 对么?
You knew her right?
哦 对关系不错 现在还是
[Jack] Oh yeah. Real well. Still do.
我很担心你 迈尔斯
I'm worried about you Miles.
你需要钱么?
Do you need some money?
杰克
Jack.
杰克 过来
Jack come on.
[TV:橡皮袋食品容器? ]
[TV:Man] A rubber bag food slinger?
[你不是在开玩笑吧? ]
Are you kidding me?
[超神奇的树上小屋…]
Our super - amazing tree house...
[由我们的2x4技术带给您…]
brought about by ourtwo - by - four technology...
杰克!别 别 别会把她弄醒的
[Whispers] Jack! No no no no. She'll wake up.
[谁干的? ]
Who did this?
- [我干的!] - [什么? ]
- [Boy] I did! - [Man] What?
[她太累了 傻瓜]
She was tired silly.
[我们的船真高!]
Our ship was so high!
[他们需要一次度假!]
[Girl] They need a vacation!
[仓鼠假日!大家都开心!]
Hamster holiday! Fun for all!
靠!大早上的干那个是不是太早了? 你明白我的意思么?
Fuck! Too early in the morning for that.You know what I mean?
哦 她只是个孩子 看在上帝的份上
Oh. She's a kid for God's sake.
好像她会喜欢我们这样的男人似的
As if she would even be attractedto guys like us in the first place.
是在说你自己吧 我可是总有靓妞注意的 各种年龄段的
Speak for yourself man. I get chickslooking at me all the time. All ages.
甚至包括男人
Dudes too.
喂 这样不值得你要付出很大代价
Well it's not worth it.You pay too big a price.
- 没有什么是免费的 - 你需要被操一顿 迈尔斯
- It's never free. - You need to get laid Miles.
这将是这星期我送给你的伴郎礼物
- [Laughs] - That's gonna be my best - man giftto you this week.
我要让你被操一顿
I'm gonna get you laid.
太好了
Wonderful.
我不会给你送什么礼券啊 袖珍小刀啊这样的狗屎东西
I'm not gonna get you a gift certificateor a penknife or any of that other horseshit.
- 我宁可要个小刀 - 不
- I'd rather have a knife. - No.
你已经被真真正正压抑了大概两年了
You have been officially depressedfor like two years now.
反正你就是个消极的人 在大学时就那样
You're a negative guy anyway even back in college.
- 唔 - 现在变得更糟了
- Mm - hmm. - And now it's worse.
你真是屈才给他妈的8年级学生教英语?
You're wasting away. Teaching Englishto fucking eighth - graders?
他们什么时候能读到你写的东西你的书 迈尔斯
When they oughta be reading what you wrote.Your books Miles.
- 我正在努力 - 努力的还不够
- I'm working on it. - [Mutters] Not working hard enough.
- 你还在看那个心理医生么? - 我每周一去看
- Are you still seeing that shrink? - I saw him on Monday.
我大部分时间都花在帮他整电脑上了
I spent most of the timehelping him with his computer.
哼 我得说去他妈的心理治疗…你在吃什么药? 阿普唑仑?
Well I say fuck therapy and...What is that stuff you take? Xanax?
对 还有百忧解
And Lexapro yes.
哼 这些药也去他妈的你需要的是活动活动关节 迈尔斯
Well I say fuck that too.You need to get your joint worked on Miles.
好了 杰克…杰克…
Okay Jack...Jack... [Clears Throat]
这个星期不是为我的 而是为你的
This week is not about me.It is about you.
我要让你享受一段美妙时光
I'm gonna show you a good time.
我们要喝很多很多美酒 我们要打高尔夫…
We're gonna drink a lot of good wine we're gonna play some golf...
我们要吃山珍海味 欣赏美景…
we're gonna eat some great food enjoy the scenery...
我们要像模像样的和你告别 mon frere 我的兄弟
and we're gonna send you off in style mon frere.
要让你的骨头都被亲遍
And get your bone smooched.
这么着
You know what?
我们从圣罗莎路出口走 先去斯坦福酒园怎么样?
Let's take the Santa Rosa Road exitand hit Sanford first. Okay?
我觉得不错 我正需要喝一杯
Sounds good to me. I need a drink.
他们生产顶尖的皮诺酒和夏多利(chardonnay)酒
These guys make top - notch pinotand chardonnay.
是圣巴巴拉一带最好的产酒地之一
One of the best producersin Santa Barbara County.
- 我还以为你讨厌夏多利酒呢 - 不 不不 我喜欢所有单品葡萄酒
- I thought you hated chardonnay. - No no no. I like all varietals.
我只是不怎么喜欢加利福尼亚处理夏多利酒的方式
I just don't generally like the waythey manipulate chardonnay in California.
- 用太多橡木和苹果酸发酵 - 哈
- Too much oak and secondarymalolactic fermentation. - Huh.
你看 这个地区很适合皮诺葡萄的原因…
You see the reason that this regionis so good for pinot...
是晚间从太平洋来的冷空气…
is that the cold air off the Pacificflows in at night...
让浆果类植物凉快下去
and it just cools down the berries.
皮诺是一种皮很薄的葡萄
Pinot's a very thin - skinned grape.
不喜欢持久高温和潮湿非常娇贵
It doesn't like constant heat or humidity.Very delicate.
我演示给你看该怎么做
[Miles] Let me show you how this is done.
首先…举起杯子对着灯光仔细看葡萄酒
First thing... hold the glass up andexamine the wine against the light.
你要看的是颜色和纯净度
You're looking for color and clarity.
- 感觉一下它好了么? - 好了
- Just get a sense of it. Okay? - Okay.
是稠还是稀? 是水状还是浆状?
Thick? Thin? Watery? Syrupy?
- 好了么? - 好了
- Okay? - Okay.
现在倾斜一点
Now tip it.
现在要做的是在它靠近杯边缘稀薄的地方检查颜色的密度
What you're doing here is checking for colordensity as it thins out towards the rim.
这会告诉你酒有多陈 当然还有其他的
That's gonna tell you how old it is among other things.
通常这对红酒更加重要
It's usuallymore important with reds.
- 好了么? - 好了
- Okay? - Okay.
现在把鼻子伸进去
Now stick your nose in it.
- 对么? - 不要害羞
- [Sniffs] Yeah? - Don't be shy.
真的要把鼻子放进去真的…
Really get your nose right in there.Really...
呒 一点橘子味
Mmm. A little citrus.
好像还有点草莓呒
Maybe some strawberry. Mmm.
西番莲果呒
Passion fruit. Mmm.
还有… 啊 好像还有点 非常淡的…
And... Ah there's just like the faintest...
很轻微的 像芦笋 还有…
[Sniffs] soupcon of like uh asparagus and...
有那么点隐隐约约的 像…
There's a...just a flutter of like a...
像 坚果伊顿奶酪
like a nutty Edam cheese.
哇
- Wow. - [Sniffs]
呒
Mmm!
- 草莓对 - 好
- Strawberries. Yeah. - Good.
- 草莓而已没有奶酪 - 好吧
- Strawberries. Not the cheese. - All right.
放下杯子让它进点空气
Put your glass down.Get some air into it.
氧化能将它打开
Oxygenating it opens it up.
释放出香气和滋味非常重要
It unlocks the aromas the flavors.Very important.
再闻
- Smell again. - [Both Inhaling]
啊对每一杯都要这样做
Ah. That's what you dowith every one of'em.
- 哇那我们什么时候才能喝? - 现在
- Wow. When do we drink it? - Now.
呒!啊
Mmm! Ahh.
- 呒 - 你给这个酒打几分 迈尔斯?
- Mmm. - How would you rate this one Miles?
嗯 通常他们一开始给你的酒都像给有学习障碍的人准备的…
Well usually they start you on wineswith learning disabilities...
不过这个确实很好
but this one is pretty damn good.
- 这个是新酒 对吧 克里斯? - 两个月前才出的
- This is the new one. Right Chris? - Just released two months ago.
- 很不错 - 我们都喜欢
- Nice job. - We like it.
你可以在葡萄酒店工作 迈尔斯 迈尔斯
You could work in a wine store Miles.
唔 是啊 可能是个好出路
Mmm. Yeah.That'd be a good move.
你在嚼口香糖么?
Are you chewing gum?
你觉得我和克莉丝汀结婚会不会是个错误?
Do you think I'm making a mistakemarrying Christine?
哇呜!
Whoa!
你觉得我做的对么 迈尔斯? 说实话
Do you think I'm doing the right thing Miles?Tell me the truth.
我的意思是 你是过来人
I mean you've been there.
嗯 是这样 我认为你曾经的等待很有道理…
Well you know I... I think that youwaited for some good reason...
你向克莉丝汀求婚也很有道理…
and that you proposed to Christinefor some good reason...
所以我觉得这是很好的事
so I think it's great.
是时候了
It's time.
我是说 你得把眼睛睁大点 这就行了
I mean you gotta have your eyes open that's all.
我的意思是 你看看我我原以为我和维多利亚能安稳过一辈子
I mean look at me.I thought Victoria and I were set for life.
克莉丝汀的爸爸 他居然跟我谈了…
Christine's dad he's really been talking to me...
让我加入他的房地产生意 传授给我其中的窍门
about bringing me into his property business showing me the ropes.
这可意义重大想想他用了多长时间才接受了我不是亚美尼亚人的事实
Which is something considering how longit took him to get over my not being Armenian.
所以我总在想
So I'm thinking about it.
不过我也不知道
But I don't know.
可能会有点乱
Might get a little incestuous.
不过迈克做的很好很多高端的商业东西
But Mike does great.A lot of high - end commercial stuff.
- 那你以后就放弃表演了? - 不可能 不会
- So you're gonna stop acting? - No way! No.
这只是为了生活稳定
This would just provide some stability.
我总能挤出时间 时不时参加个广告或者试演什么的
I could always squeeze in a commercialor an audition here there.
我得保持状态 万一好机会来了呢
Keep myself in the game in casesomething really great came along.
我们都不再年轻了 迈尔斯
We're not getting any younger Miles.
对 不再了
No. No.
嗨 嗨 嗨!嗨
- Hey hey hey.! - Hey.
- 迈尔斯! - 先生
- Miles! - Sir.
- 好久不见了 - 盖理 很高兴见到你
- Long time no see. - Gary nice to see you.
- 你的小说什么时候出来? 我们都等着读呢 - 马上了 马上了
- When's your novel coming out?We all wanna read it. - Soon soon soon.
这是我的老朋友 杰克 他下星期要结婚了
This is my buddyJack.He's getting married next week.
我哀悼一下 伙计你们今晚去哪里喝?
- My condolences man. - What are you pouring tonight?
- 呃 我们有很多上等货 - 嗯哼?
- Uh we have got a lot of good stuff. - Mm - hmm?
啊 我们有 呃 新的Bien Nacido酒想尝尝么?
Ah we have the uh new Bien Nacido.You want a taste?
那当然
[Laughs] Absolument.
他们这儿生产自己的酒 绝对不同凡响
They make their own wine here.It's just outstanding.
很独特谢谢
Very special. Thank you.
呒!
Mmm!
- 呒 - 你觉得怎么样?
- Mmm. - So what do you think?
比修女的xx还要紧浓度很好 原料不错
Tighter than a nun's asshole.But good concentration. Nice fruit.
给我们倒两杯 好么
Pour us a couple will ya.
对 是很烈
Yeah. It's tight.
给 先生们
There you are gentlemen.
这瓶留给你了很高兴见到你
I will leave you the bottle.And it is good to see you.
嗨 伙计为我最后一周的自由
Hey man.Here's to my last week of freedom.
会很好的
It's gonna be great.
为我们俩
Here's to us.
- 迈尔斯 - 嗯哼?
- Miles. - Mm - hmm?
看那个小妞
Check out that chick.
哦那是玛雅
Oh. Yeah. That's Maya.
- 你认识她? - 当然 我认识玛雅
- You know her? - Sure I know Maya.
- 你认识那个妞? - 是的 杰克我每次过来都在这儿吃饭
- You know that chick? - Yes.Jack this is where I eatwhen I come up here.
懂么? 这儿就好像我的办公室
You know?It's practically my office.
偶尔我会和在这儿工作的人喝一杯 就是这样
And occasionally I have a drinkwith the employees yeah.
玛雅非常棒 她在这里工作了一年 一年半了
Maya's great.She's worked here a year year and a half.
她性感的让人难以置信
She's incredibly hot.
对 她是的她很好 不过已经结婚了
Yes she is.And nice. And married.
看她的大钻戒
Check out the rock.
哦 那个屎都不算
Oh that doesn't mean shit.
克莉丝汀在寿司店工作的时候…
When Christine worked at Sushi Roku...
她一直戴着大个的订婚戒指 以防男人们挑逗她
she wore a big engagement ringto keep guys from hitting on her.
有用么? 他妈一点用没有你以为我是怎么认识她的?
Think it worked? Fuck no.How do you think I met her?
嗯 这个女孩嫁的可是加州圣巴巴拉大学的哲学教授
Well this gal is married to somephilosophy professor at U.C. Santa Barbara.
教授的太太做女招待说明什么? 明显婚姻完蛋了
What's a professor's wife doing waitressing?Obviously that's over.
杰克 你并不了解这个女人
Jack you don't know anythingabout this woman.
冷静点吃饭吧
Calm down. Let's just eat.
- 嗨 迈尔斯! - 哦 嗨 玛雅
- Hey Miles! - Oh! Hi Maya.
- 你好么? - 我很好 很好
- How are you? - I'm good. Good.
你看上气色不错是不是减肥了?
You look great.Did you lose some weight?
呃…事实上 没有
Uh... no actually.
可是… 谢谢
But... thank you. [Chuckles]
- 晚上很忙 嗯? - 星期天嘛
- Busy night huh? - Sunday.
你们俩出来品酒的?
You guys been out tasting?
哦 你说对了 说对了
Oh you know it. You know it.
哦 这是我的朋友 杰克 杰克 这是玛雅
Oh this is my friend Jack.Jack Maya.
- 嗨 玛雅 - 嗨
- Hiya. - Hi.
那 很高兴见到你再见 迈尔斯
Well it's good to see you. Bye Miles.
哦 得回去工作了
Oh. Back to work.
- 上帝 她真勾魂 - 是的
- Jesus she is jammin'. - Yeah.
很明显她喜欢你
And she's obviously into you.
对她 你还了解什么?
What else do you know about her?
嗯 她很懂葡萄酒
Well she does know a lot about wine.
啊看来有戏
Ah. Now we're getting somewhere.
- 她喜欢皮诺酒 - 绝配!
- She likes pinot. - Perfect!
妈的 她只是布尔顿的一个女招待 杰克
She's a fucking waitressin Buellton Jack.
我们怎么可能?
How is that ever gonna work out?
你这家伙怎么你总是盯着坏的一面?
You dick. Why do you have tofocus on the negative?
- 看看她对你多亲切? - 她只是为了小费
- See how friendly she was to you? - She works for tips.
你瞎了 伙计瞎了
You're blind dude. Blind.
我还推荐鸵鸟排骨肉很瘦是本地养的
I can also recommend the ostrich steak.Very lean. Locally raised.
嗨 盖理
Hey Gary.
- 再来点Highliner酒 - 好的
- Highliner please. - You got it.
- 我们请了 - 是的 真的
- That's on us. - Yes indeed.
嗨 大家介意么?
Well hey guys. Do you mind?
- 哦 不不 - 你确定?
- Oh no no no. - You sure?
请便点吧 点吧
Please. Light up light up.
事实上 你愿意和我们坐一起么?
In fact would you like to join us?
当然
Sure.
嗯 你的书怎么样了 迈尔斯?
- [Clears Throat] - So how's that book coming Miles?
我想上次我们聊的时候你差不多快完成了
I think you were almost finished with itthe last time we talked.
- 我已经完成了 - 你真棒!喔
- I finished it. - Good for you! Wow.
现在正在出版
It's getting published.
这就是 呃 我们为什么到这儿来庆祝
That's uh actually whywe're up here celebrating.
喔 祝贺你
Well congratulations.
- 这真是妙极了! - 是啊
- That's fantastic! - Yeah.
- 干杯 - 谢谢
- Cheers. - Thanks.
你也是作家么?
Are you a writer too?
不 玛雅 我是个演员
No Maya I'm an actor.
真的? 演什么?
Really. What kind of stuff?
呒 很多电视
Mmm a lot ofTV.
我原来是几个剧集的常规演员
I used to be a regularon a couple of series.
不过最近就是演很多广告大部分是给侨民做的
But lately it's been a lot of commercial work.Nationals mostly.
有没有我可能知道的?
Anything I might know?
可能这个有没有印象?
Perhaps. Do you recognize this?
现在只有很低 很低 58%的年利率
Now with a low low5.8% A.P.R. financing!
太好笑了!
[Laughing] That's hilarious!
- 你听上去很象那种人 - 我就是那种人
- You sound just like one of those guys. - Am one of those guys.
- 你不是 - 他是的
- You are not. - He is.
使用本产品前 请咨询医生
Consult your doctorbefore using this product.
副作用包括出油…
Side effects may include oily discharge...
麻疹 食欲不振 低血压
hives loss of appetite low blood pressure.
如果你有糖尿病或肾病史…
If you have diabetesor a history of kidney trouble...
你必死无疑 笨蛋!
you're dead asshole!
对
[Chuckles] Yeah.
那 你们今天晚上打算干什么?
So what are you guys up to tonight?
哦 我们已经挺累了
Oh we're pretty wiped.
我想我们就回汽车旅馆睡觉
I think we're just gonna go backto the motel and crash.
对我想开车来这儿有很长的路吧
Yeah I guess it'skind of a long drive up here.
- 呒 - 你们住哪里?
- Mmm. - Where are you staying?
呃 '风车'
Uh the Windmill.
'风车'
Windmill.
这女孩想要个派对…
The girl is looking to party...
你却告诉她我们要回汽车旅馆睡觉?
and you tell her we're going backto the motel and crash?
- 上帝啊 迈尔斯! - 唉 我累了 杰克
- Jesus Miles! - Well I'm tired Jack.
- 你难道不累么? - 那个女孩在试探你 笨蛋!
- Aren't you tired? - The chick digs you man!
她容光焕发象个弹球机…
She lit up like a pinball machine...
在她听说你的小说要出版的时候
when she found outyour novel was getting published.
现在我不得不活在另一个谎言中
Now I have another lie to live down.
- 谢谢你 杰克 - 我只是想让你行动起来
- Thanks Jack. - Just trying to get you a little action.
我就很乐意接受一些帮助
I would appreciate a little bit of help.
我不觉得你那是在帮我 你把她全忘了
Didn't seem to me like that's whatwas going on. You were all over her.
噢 你就一定要教训我
Well somebody had to do the talking.
而且 我猜对了…她的婚姻完了
And by the way I was right...she's not married.
- 你怎么知道 - 没钻戒
- How do you know? - No rock.
她在酒吧的时候没戴钻戒
When she came to the bar she was sans rock.
哦
Oh.
今天的计划是什么 迈尔斯?
What's the plan for today Miles?
阿哈
Aha.
好呃 我们先朝北去…
Good. Um we head up north...
从那儿开始我们的葡萄之旅…
Begin the grape tour up there...
一路往南…
work our way south...
这样 我们喝的越多…
so that the more we drink...
就离我们的汽车旅馆越近
the closer we get to the motel.
你到底有什么问题?
What's your problem?
怎么了?
What is it?
我这次旅程一定要找点刺激 迈尔斯…
I'm going to get my nuton this trip Miles...
你别坏我的事…
and you are not gonnafuck it up for me...
别用你那些沮丧 焦虑 那些他妈的负面思想
with all of your depression and anxietyand neg - head downer shit.
哦
[Chuckles] Oh.
好啊 你都摊牌了
Well now the cards are on the table.
对 没错
Yes they are.
- 啊 - 我是认真的别坏我的事 迈尔斯
- Ah. - And I am serious. Do not fuck with me Miles.
我要在周六结婚前操一顿 你懂不懂?
I am going to get laid before I get marriedon Saturday. Do you read me?
懂 老大 当然懂
Sure big guy. Absolutely.
你讲的每个字都声音又大又清楚
Loud and clear.Whatever you say.
显然 你在为你想要得派对生气
It's uh your party evidently.
你为什么不干脆 呃…
Why don't you just uh...
呃 对 你为什么不干脆自己去 我可以搭火车回去
Uh yeah. Why don't you just go out and I'll catch a train back.
不 迈尔斯!
No Miles!
伙计 这周我们要疯狂
Man this is our week to get crazy.
我们两个都要放纵一下
We should both be cutting loose.
这是我们最后的机会了这是我们的一星期 伙计
This could be our last chance.This is our week man.
我们必须分享
It's something we should share.
这是我们的席拉(Syrah)酒
[Man] This is our Syrah.
好
Okay.
- 喔! - 好吧? 喜欢么?
- Ooh! - Yeah? Like that?
这个味很重
That's a big one.
这酒要连葡萄皮一起在一个开口的酒桶中放两个星期
[Woman] But it did sit with the skins forabout two weeks in an open - topped tank.
- 难怪有单宁酸味儿 对不? - 是啊 这酒还很新
- So that would explain all the tannins no? - Well it is a young wine.
- 就是说当酒越放越陈 单宁酸就会挥散掉 - 对 当然
- So as the wine ages the tannins will dissipate. - Right. Of course.
- 抱歉等我一下 - 真是好东西
- Excuse me for just a minute. - Good stuff.
呒 倒满 小家伙
Mmm. Fill up there bub.
这是我们园子的夏多利(chardonnay)酒
[Woman] This is our estate chardonnay.
哇 这个女孩才懂得怎么倒酒你叫什么?
Now there's a girl who knows how to pour.What's your name?
斯蒂芬妮
Stephanie.
斯蒂芬妮 好听
Stephanie. Nice.
你觉得怎么样?
So what do you think?
呒 可以一饮而尽
Mmm. Quaffable.
不过离卓越还差很多
But uh far from transcendent.
我喜欢味道很好
I like it. Tastes great.
行了
Oak - y.
这个是品丽珠红葡萄酒(cabernet franc)
This is a cabernet franc.
我们生产这种单品葡萄酒才第五年
This is only the fifth yearwe've made this varietal.
周围很少有酒园子做纯的品丽珠红酒
Very few wineries around heredo a straight cab franc.
这是产自我们在圣玛丽的葡萄园…
It's from our vineyardsup in Santa Maria...
得过一次银质奖…
and it was a silver medal winner...
去年得了帕索罗布奖
at Paso Robles last year.
嗯
Hmm.
呒
Mmm.
那么 我想说的是
Well I will tell you something.
我从来就没觉得品丽珠红酒有什么妙处 这次也不例外
I've come never to expect greatness froma cab franc and this one is no different.
有一种空洞的 松弛的 熟过头的感觉…
It's kind of a hollow flabby overripe...
我不知道对我来说味道不错
I don't know.Tastes pretty good to me.
那 呃 你住这附近么 斯蒂芬妮?
So um do you live around here Stephanie?
对 就在洛斯阿拉莫斯附近我同意你对品丽珠红酒的评价
Yeah up around Los Alamos.And I agree with you about cab franc.
我们刚去过布尔顿酒园
We're just over in Buellton.
风车旅馆
The Windmill Inn.
- 哦 是么? - 嗯
- Oh yeah? - Mmm.
你有没有碰巧认识一个叫玛雅的女孩 她在The Hitching Post酒吧工作?
Do you happen to know a gal named Mayathat works at The Hitching Post?
- 当然 我认识玛雅 我和她很要好 - 真的? 没骗人?
- Yeah. Sure. I know Maya. I know her real well. - Yeah? No shit?
我们昨天晚上和她一起喝酒了迈尔斯认识她
We had a drink with her last night.Miles knows her.
对我们能不能继续尝席拉酒?
Yes. Could we move onto the Syrah please?
哦等不及了 嗯?
Oh. Champing at the bit huh?
当然
Sure.
这个是我们园子的席拉酒
This is our estate Syrah.
你真是个坏坏的女孩 斯蒂芬妮
You are a bad bad girl Stephanie.
我知道 我应该被打屁屁
I know. I need to be spanked.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
席拉?
The Syrah?
嘿 嘿 打开车后箱
Hey. Hey. Get the trunk.
- 你掏钥匙 - 我有钥匙么?
- You have the keys. - I do?
- 对 - 在我口袋里
- Yeah. - In my pocket.
- 这么说 我们成了 - 什么
- So we're on. - What?
对呀她去叫玛雅 她今晚不工作我们一起出去
Yeah. She called Maya who's not workingtonight. So we're all going out.
- 和 和玛雅? - 对
- Wi... With Maya? - Yeah.
她离婚已经一年了 伙计
She's been divorced a year now buddy.
那个叫斯蒂芬妮得女孩?
This chick Stephanie?
她什么都安排好了
She's got it all goin' on.
嗯 她很可爱 对
Well she is cute yeah.
可爱? 她是他妈的辣妹
Cute? She's a fuckin' hottie.
你差点就告诉她我要结婚了? 你怎么了你?
And you almost tell her that I'm gettin' married?What's the matter with you?
- 很漂亮 噢? - 非常美
- Nice huh? - It's beautiful.
对维多利亚和我原来很喜欢这里
Yeah. Victoria and Iused to like this view.
你知道 有一次我们在这里野餐…
You know once we had a picnic here...
我们喝了一瓶95年的作品一号
and we drank a '95 Opus One.
就着烟熏三文鱼和蓟菜不过我们不在乎
With smoked salmon and artichokes.But we didn't care.
噢 天哪 她是我认识的味觉最好的女人
Oh man she has the best palateof any woman I have ever known.
她可以分辨出所有不同种类的意大利葡萄酒
She can even differentiateall different kinds of Italian wines.
迈尔斯 有些事我必须告诉你
- Miles there's something I gotta tell you. - [Sighs]
维多利亚也要来参加婚礼
Victoria's coming to the wedding.
对 我知道你告诉过我的我不介意
Yeah I know. You told me.I'm all right with it.
是的 不过我没全告诉你
Yeah but that's not the whole story.
她已经再婚了
She got remarried.
她什么?
She what?
什么时候?
When?
大概一个月以前
About a month ago.
可能6个星期
Maybe six weeks.
嫁给那个家伙…那个开餐馆的家伙?
To that guy...that guy with the restaurant?
迈尔斯?
Miles?
迈尔斯
Miles.
我想回家了
I'd like to go home now.
迈尔斯 从车里下来
Miles get out of the car.
请开车送我会旅馆
Would you drive meback to the motel please?
你知道…
[Sighs] You know...
她要带他来参加婚礼?
She bringing him to the wedding?
你觉得怎么样?
What do you think?
你为什么不早点告诉我 杰克?
Why didn't you tell meabout this before Jack?
因为我知道你肯定要发疯了那我们就不能一起来者趟旅行了
Because I knew you'd get so freaked outthat you wouldn't even come on this trip.
然后我想 这可能是我告诉你这件事最好的地方
But then I thought this is the perfect place to tell you.
我们来这里就是为了忘掉那些狗屎事我们来这里就是为了派对的 伙计
We're here to forget about all that shit.We're here to party man.
我是个可怜虫
I'm gonna be a fucking pariah.
不受欢迎的人
Persona non grata.
每个人都会屏住呼吸 等着看我喝多了出洋相
Everybody's gonna be holding their breath waiting to see if I get drunk and make a scene.
不 不 不 你看
No no. No. Look.
我和维多利亚谈过了 好么?
I talked to Victoria. Okay?
她很好每个人都很好
She's cool. Everybody's cool.
对不起 你已经和她谈过了…
I'm sorry. You've been talking...
背着我…
Behind my back...
你们谈论?
you've been talking about it?
你干什么?
What are you doing?
回来
Come back here.
迈尔斯
Miles!
- 回来把酒瓶给我 - 退后 杰克
- Come here. Give me that bottle. - Back off Jack.
- 好了… - 退后 笨蛋!
- Come on... Back off man!
- 把酒瓶给我 - 不
- Give me that bottle. - No.
迈尔斯
Miles.
Miles!
[TV: 很多人认为他们能成功]
[TV:Announcer] A lot of peopleout there think they can make it.
[生活中还有什么比敢于追求梦想更好的? ]
What better thing in life is to chase thedream and not be afraid of going after it?
[詹姆斯·里普 接下来上演]
James Lepp next to play.Chance for a birdie and a five - shot lead.
我要去游泳 让血液流通你来么?
I'm gonna go for a swim get the blood flowing. You wanna come?
不 我想看电视
No. I wanna watch this.
好吧
Okay.
[应该把球放在左边一两英寸外]
Should start this ball one or two inchesoutside the left edge.
[进去]
[Spectator Whispers] Go in.
[观众欢呼]
[Crowd Groans]
- [漂亮的一击] - [绝对漂亮 速度很好]
- [Announcer] Great putt. - [Analyst] Absolutely. Great speed.
迈尔斯
Miles.
哦 迈尔斯 该起床了
Oh Miles. Time to get up.
靠 那个女孩在按摩浴缸里…
This fuckin' chick in theJacuzzi...
哦 好家伙!
Oh dude!
那个地方很宽敞 我就打算在那儿干 伙计
This place is wide open.I'm goin' fuckin' nuts up here man.
- 嘿 我应该穿什么? - 我不知道
- Hey what should I wear? - I don't know.
休闲一些的 不过要好看她们觉得你是个作家
Something casual but nice.They think you're a writer.
好的 好的
[Mutters] Right. Okay.
呒
Mmm.
你还有没有别的鞋了?
Do you have any other shoes?
呃 - 呃
Uh - uh.
嗯
Hmm.
嗨 亲爱的
- [Exhales] - Hey honey.
噢 我就是打电话问问你怎么样了
Yeah I was just calling to check in.
我和迈尔斯要准备出去吃晚饭了
Miles and I are getting readyto go to dinner.
可能要在外面待很晚 所以我想现在打电话给你说晚安
Probably stay out late so I just thoughtI'd call and say good night now.
是的 我也想你
Yeah. I miss you too.
是的 我也爱你
Yeah. I love you too.
尽量像你正常时候一样 幽默一点 好么?
Just try to be your normal humorous self. Okay?
像你感情崩溃前那样你还记得那个时候的你么?
The guy you were before the tailspin.Do you remember that guy?
大家都喜欢那个时候的你
People love that guy.
而且别忘了…你的小说秋天就要面市了
And don't forget...your novel is coming out in the fall.
哦 真的么? 多么让人激动啊叫什么名字?
Oh. Really? How exciting.What's it called?
过来 迈尔斯 过来
Come here Miles. Come here.
不要破坏我的事
Do not sabotage me.
如果你想当他妈的烂人 你就自己当烂人
If you wanna be a fuckin' lightweight then that's your call.
- 但是不要破坏我 - 哦 是 是 船长我保证
- But do not sabotage me. - Oh aye aye cap'n. You got it.
如果她们想喝梅乐酒 我们就喝梅乐酒
And if they wanna drink merlot we're drinkin' merlot.
如果谁要是点了梅乐酒 我马上走人我才不喝他妈的merlot呢!
If anybody orders merlot I'm leaving.I am not drinking any fucking merlot!
好了 好了 放松 迈尔斯
Okay okay. Relax Miles.
上帝啊 不要梅乐酒
Jesus. No merlot.
你有没有带你的抗抑郁药?
Did you bring your Xanax?
好的
- [Pills Rattle] - All right.
过来
Come here.
别喝太多听见没?
Do not drink too much.Do you hear me?
我可不想你醉倒 或撒酒疯
I don't want you passing outor going to the dark side.
- 不撒酒疯! - 好的
- No going to the dark side! - Okay!
嗨我们找朋友
Hi.Just looking for some friends.
晚上好 女士们你们好么?
Good evening ladies.How are you?
- 嗨 迈尔斯 - 很好 你呢?
- Hi Miles. - [Stephanie] Good. How are you?
你好 玛雅 你好 玛雅
Hello Maya. [Sighs]
- 你看上去美极了你们俩都是 - 谢谢
- You look gorgeous. You both do. - [Maya] Thank you.
- 你自己也不错 - 谢谢 谢谢
- You're not so bad yourself. - Thanks. Thanks.
那 这有什么好酒?
[Jack] So what's good here?
- 你们喝的是什么? - 哦 这个是长相思(sauvignon blanc)
- What is this you're drinking? - Oh this is the Fiddlehead sauvignon blanc.
- 啊 知道了好喝么? - 你试试
- Ah I see. Is it good? - Try it.
- 你们酒吧几点关 叫什么来着? - 卡里拉
- What time did you close up at Ka... Is it... Kalyra.
- 卡里拉 - 其实我很顺利就出来了 大概5:30 6点的样子
- Kalyra. - I actually got out of there pretty good around 5:30 6:00.
- 还有点事情要做 - 迈尔斯和我 我俩…
- Still had some stuff to do. - Miles and I we were...
- 很好 - 这是在橡木中放了12个月的
- That's nice. - It's aged 1 2 months in oak.
- 法国橡木 - 长相思酒?
- French oak. - Sauvignon blanc?
嗯 有趣很好
Huh. Interesting. It's good.
我认识这个造酒商她经常去我们餐厅
I know the winemaker.She comes into the restaurant all the time.
- 你关门前都要干什么? - 我要关闭登记处
- What do you have to do to close up? - I close up the register.
打扫一下 把一些东西放好再把第二天的酒杯准备好
Clean up put some stuff away.Then put the glasses out for the next day.
- 对 - 就是些…小事
- Right. - Just... small stuff.
有一点点丁香味
Uh hints of clove.
- 对么? - 是的 我知道 我很喜欢
- Right? - Yes! I know. I love that.
对呒
Yeah. Mmm.
对不起很好
Sorry. It's good.
- 没关系我们再给你要一杯 - 啊 我们要开喝了
- No no. We'll get you a glass. - Ah! Now we're thinking.
好
Good. [Chuckles] Okay.
哦 那个…那个…
[Stephanie] Oh that's... that...
哦 他可以说出来呀 不是很恶心
Oh he can say it and it's not disgusting?
我没听见他说
I didn't hear him say that.
- 每次我重复他说的话… - 非常好
- Whenever I say something he said... [Laughs] Very good.
不 事实上 是那个不是这个…
No actually... No. That one.N - Not this one...
我也有那个
[Jack] I'm having that too.
- 什么? - 哦 是的
- Right? - Oh yes.
那是我要说的
That's what I'm saying.
汤我们有玉米杂烩…
For our soup we have corn chowder...
主菜我们有大猪排浇太妃糖…
and for our entrees we have medallionsof pork dusted with black truffles...
配菜有菜根和芥末土豆
served with a root vegetable foulonand wasabi whipped potatoes.
最后…
And finally...
- 我不得不解释我的证件 - 对!
- [Maya] I have to explain my credentials. - [Stephanie] Yes.!
迈尔斯 这个让你想起什么?
Miles what does this remind you of?.
"红酒 红酒"
"Red wine. Red wine."
他是在一大堆指责中长大的
[Jack] He was brought up on a lot of charges.
- 是么? - 我的意思是警告
- Yeah? - I mean with the yellow light.
对
Right.
总之 今晚我们要庆祝迈尔斯的新书
After all tonightwe are celebrating Miles's book deal.
- 出版作家 - 哦 哇!
- Published author. - Oh! Wow!
哇呜 迈尔斯!
Wow Miles.!
- 哦! - 那么 那样的话…
- Ohh.! - [Maya] Well in that case...
然后他们就以为你没有任何想法 无法控制局面
And then they think you have no idea.You have no control over it.
古老的处理葡萄的方式
[Miles] Ancient way of treating the grape.
现在这种是现代的处理葡萄的方式
Now it's a modern wayof treating the grape.
那时传统的酿酒方式 一种有争议的方式
It's a traditional way of dealing with wine.It's a controversial way.
然后大家都回去了
[Stephanie] So everyone's going back to that.
只是总有些重叠的地方
It's just that there'sa certain constant lapping.
- 那个不是…那是个钓鱼的湖 - 嗯哼
- It's not a... It's a fishing lake. - Mm - hmm.
你的嘴唇很柔软
Your lips look soft.
- 总的来说… - 哦 不你的意思是 好比 这个是干什么用的?
- The whole area is... Oh no. You mean like what it was used for?
- 他们为什么要打电话…
- What do they call the... [Phone:Line Continues Ringing]
马里布…是马里布峡谷
Malibu... It's Malibu Canyon.
我也不知道我到底想说什么
I don't know what the hellI'm trying to say.
喂?
- [Line Picks Up] - [Woman] Hello?
维多利亚?
Victoria?
迈尔斯?
Miles?
好 好 好 好维多利亚 你怎么样啊?
Well well well well well.Victoria. How the hell are ya?
什么…呃…你想干什么?
What... Uh... What's on your mind?
哦 没什么我…
Oh nothin'. I... [Chuckles]
刚听说你又结婚了
Just heard that you got remarried.
恭喜啊我 呃…
Congratulations. I uh...
哦 我可没想到你还有胃口再来一遍
Boy I didn't think you had the stomachfor another go - around.
哦 迈尔斯 你喝醉了
Oh Miles you're drunk.
噢 就一点本地的皮诺 你知道的
Oh just a little local pinot you know.
一点勃艮第(burgundy) 那种老的法国伯尔尼红酒(Cotes de Beaune)
A little burgundy. That old Cotes de Beaune. [Laughs Clears Throat]
- 你在哪里? - 呃 一个洛杉矶奥利沃斯的小地方
- Where are you? - Uh a little place in Los Olivos.
店主是新的 环境很温馨 呃…
New owners. Cozy ambience uh...
吃的东西也非常好你应该 呃…你应该试试
Excellent food too.You should uh... You should try it.
我想起了你 呃昨天晚上在Hitching Post的时候
I thought of you at the uh Hitching Post last night.
喂?
Hello?
- 迈尔斯 不要在喝醉的时候给我打电话 - 没有 只是…
- Miles don't call me when you're drunk. - No it's...
好吧 我只是…想让你知道…
All right I just...I wanted to let you know...
我已经决定不去参加婚礼了…
that I have decidednot to come to the wedding...
所以 如果你原来担心会发生什么像吵架这种事
so just in case you were dreading some sort of you know run - in or something like that...
那你现在不用再担心了…
well you worry no more...
因为我不会去那儿的
because I'm not gonna be there.
这是个小小的结婚礼物 送给你和…他叫什么来着
It's my little wedding giftto you and what's - his - name.
他叫什么?
What is his name?
肯
Ken.
肯!太好了
Ken! Right.
肯
Ken.
我要挂了 迈尔斯
I'm gonna hang up now Miles.
不…你知道 只不过…我刚听说这件事…
No... You know it's just...I - I - I heard about this...
今天第一次听说
for the first time uh today.
呃 你又结婚了就是这样
Uh your getting remarried that is.
呃 我就是有点吓到了
And uh I was kind of taken aback.
真是…难以置信
Just... hard to believe.
我原来还以为可能还有一点点希望…
I guess I thought maybethere was still a chance...
没准儿什么时候我们俩
for us somewhere down the road.
我就是 呃…
And I just uh... [Sighs]
- 迈尔斯 - 嗯?
- Miles. - Huh?
也许你不去婚礼更好一些
Maybe it is betterif you don't come to the wedding.
没问题 维姬 你怎么说都行
All righty Vicki. Whatever you say.
我听你的
You're the boss.
嗯? 我不知道
Huh? I don't know.
欢迎回来
[Laughs] Welcome back.
放松点
Take it easy.
- 你还好吧 迈尔斯? - 是的 我很好
- Are you okay Miles? - Yes. I'm fine.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 失陪一下 先生们 - 失陪一下
- Excuse us gentlemen. - Excuse us.
没关系
[Jack] Sure.
- 呒 - 好的
- Mmm. - All right.
好 别太久了
Yeah. Don't take too long.
- 好的 - 好再见
- All right. - Okay. Bye girls. [Chuckles]
他妈的怎么搞得? 你怎么回事?
What the fuck?What is up with you?
- 你还记得我们再外面谈过的吧? - 对…
- You remember our little talk outside? - Yeah...
- 你他妈的打起精神来 迈尔斯 - 我没事 我没事
- Get your shit together Miles. - I'm fine. I'm fine.
你刚才去哪里了?
Where were you?
厕所
Bathroom.
你是不是有喝醉了去打电话?
Did you drink and dial?
嗯?
Hmm?
- 没有 - 你为什么老这么干?
- No. - Why do you always have to do this?
维多利亚已经飞了 飞了
Victoria is gone. Gone.
噗 消失在风里了
Poof!. In the wind.
我的意思是 你正在毁掉一个和玛雅在一起的好机会
I mean you are blowing a greatopportunity here with Maya.
玛雅…靠 玛雅…她很棒!
Maya... Fuckin' Maya... She's great!
她很好 风趣 又懂葡萄酒
She's cool she's funny she knows wine.
什么消沉郁闷的狗屎东西?
What is this morose come - down bullshit?
这些女孩要和我们派对
These girls wanna party with us.
嗯?
Huh?
还有你刚才滔滔不绝10分钟讲什么? 沃莱白葡萄酒?
And what was that 1 0 - minute lectureon what Vouvrays?
你不是开玩笑吧? 谁理你那个茬?
Are you kidding me?Who gives a fuck?
这么说吧 我对当前的整个情况很不爽
Let's just say that I'm uncomfortablewith the whole scenario.
难道你忘了和维多利亚一起的那些不愉快了么?
Have you forgotten all the bad timesyou had with Victoria...
她让你觉得你很渺小?
how small she could make you feel?
这难道不就是你先和布伦达搞婚外恋的原因么?
Isn't that why you had the affairwith Brenda in the first place?
闭嘴收起你的臭脸闭嘴
Shut up. Shut your face. Shut up.
你难道就没有注意玛雅看着你的样子么?
Have you even noticedhow Maya's looking at you?
好了 伙计你已经让她上钩了
Now come on man.You've got her on the hook.
把她钓起来钓的高一点
Reel her in.Let's ratchet this up a notch.
来 喝点冰水
Here. Drink some agua fria.
嗨!
- [Mouths Words] - Hey!
- 嗨! - 呒
- Hey! - Mmm.
啊 那 呃 我们要不要点甜点?
Ah. Well so uh shall we get some dessert?
呃 我们想 呃我们都去我家怎么样?
Uh well we were thinking um uh why don't we go back to my place?
我有葡萄酒 奶酪 音乐 什么都有
I've got wine some insane cheeses music whatever.
好呀!
[Laughs] Yeah!
- 侍者!
- [Stephanie Maya Laughing] - Waiter!
过来
Come here.
呃
Uh - huh.
- 给你一个 我三个 - 呒
- One for you three for me. - Mmm.
你确定你想这样么?
You sure you wanna do this?
- 我们来了! - 嗨!
- We're here! - [Stephanie] Hey.!
- 嗨! - 你们去哪儿了?
- Hey! - Where were you guys?
噢 我们拐错了几个弯 多亏了还有麦哲伦
Oh we took a couple of wrong turns thanks to Magellan here.
- 嗨! - 嗨!
- [Whispers] Hi. - Hi.
- 噢 迈尔斯 - 什么?
- Oh Miles. - Yeah?
- 玛雅在后面 过了厨房就是 - 好的
- Maya's in the back just past the kitchen. - Okay.
谢谢
- [Jack Chuckles] - Thanks.
嗨
Hi.
嘿
Hey.
- 哦 她有什么好酒么? - 噢 是的
- Oh has she got anything good? - Oh yeah.
斯蒂芬妮对皮诺酒和席拉酒很着迷
Steph's way into pinots and Syrahs.
- 嗨 斯蒂芬妮? - 怎么了?
- Hey Steph! - Yeah?
- 我们是不是想开哪瓶就开哪瓶? - 对对 随便
- Can we really open anything we want? - Yeah yeah. Anything.
噢 除了那瓶李其堡
Uh except the Richebourg.
李其堡? 她居然有李其堡? 好家伙
Richebourg? She has a Richebourg?Holy mackerel.
我真是低估了斯蒂芬妮了
I've completelyunderestimated Stephanie.
噢 上帝 看这个
Oh good Lord. Um look at that.
我想…这个酒更适合我们的口味
I think... this guy's more our speed.
安德鲁·默里
Andrew Murray.
好的
Well okay. All right.
那 你的收藏中有什么宝贝?
So what gems do you havein your collection?
噢 其实都算不上什么收藏
Oh it's really not muchof a collection you know.
我的意思是更像是放在柜子里的一点东西
I mean more like a small gatheringin a cabinet.
我从来没钱买那些
- [Laughs] - No I've never really had the wallet for that.
我就是忍不住要一瓶一瓶的喝
I just have to live bottle to bottle.
不过我还是省了些下来 当然了
I've got things I'm saving definitely.
我想起中的明星就是那瓶1961年的白马庄园
I guess the star would bea 1961 Cheval Blanc.
你有一瓶61年的白马庄园 却放在那里不动?
You've got a '61 Cheval Blanc and it's just sitting there?
- 是的 是的 - 快去拿
- Yes I do. - Go get it.
- 好了 - 我是认真的!快去!
- [Laughing] Okay. - I'm serious! Hurry!
好的 我会去拿的
All right. I would I would.
61年的酒现在正是最好的时候 是吧? 我从书上看的
The '61 s are peaking right now aren't they?That's what I've read.
不 对 是的
No that's right yeah.
可能都已经有点晚了你还在等什么?
It might be too late already.What are you waiting for?
噢 我不知道一个特别的场合和最合适的人
Oh I don't know.A special occasion with the right person.
- 本来是准备在结婚10周年的时候 但是… - 呒
- It was supposed to be formy 1 0th wedding anniversary but... Mmm.
你知道 当你打开61年的白马庄园的时候
You know the day you opena '6 1 Cheval Blanc...
那就是那个特别的时候
that's the special occasion.
嗯 你对葡萄酒感兴趣有多长时间了?
So uh how longhave you been into wine?
从我认真开始算起有7年了
I got serious about seven years ago.
- 是哪瓶酒让你开始的? - 88年的西施佳雅
- And what was the bottle that did it? - '88 Sassicaia.
- 啊很好恭喜 - 呒
- Ah.! Well congratulations. - Mmm.
- 是啊 - 非常好
- Yeah. - That's very good.
- 很好… - 真能让你着迷是的
- Well... That would do it. Yeah.
嗯
Hmm.
呒
Mmm.
哦 哇 真好真是非常好
Oh wow that's nice.That's very good.
我们应该多品一会儿 不过实在是味道太好了
We need to give it a minute but that's really tasty.
你觉得呢?
How about you?
我觉得他们做的有点儿过了
I think they overdid it a little.
太多酒精味儿 把葡萄的味儿都盖住了
Too much alcohol.It overwhelms the fruit.
唔
Huh.
是的 是的
Yeah. Yeah.
我得说你对钱的态度是对的
I'd say you're right on the money.
非常好很好
Very good. [Chuckles] Nice.
- 谢谢 - 呒
- Thank you. - Mmm.
呒那是斯蒂芬妮的孩子么?
Mmm! Is that Stephanie's kid?
哦 是的那是Siena
Oh. Yeah. That's Siena.
- 哦 她是个小甜心 - 很可爱 很可爱
- Oh she's a sweetie. - Cute. Cute.
她现在在哪里?
Where is she?
- 在她祖母家 - 哦
- She's at her grandmother's. - Oh.
在斯蒂芬妮的妈妈那里她经常待在那里
Steph's mom.She spends a lot of time over there.
你有孩子么?
You got kids?
哦 我? 没有 没有
Uh me? No. No.
没有 我会把他们都带坏的
- No I'd just fuck 'em up. - [Laughs]
没有 这是我的离婚中没有被污染的部分…没有孩子
No that was the one unpolluted partof my divorce... no kids.
对我也是
Yeah. Same here.
很好
Good.
我们出去吧
Let's go in there.
现在 以很低很低的4 8%的年利率…
[Jack] Now for a low low4.8% A.P.R. financing...
看起来我们的朋友们谈的很投机
Looks like our friendsare really hitting it off.
对 我也这么觉得
- Yeah I would say that. - [Laughs]
是的
- Yeah. - [Sighs]
那 你的小说是关于什么的?
- [Clears Throat] - So what's your novel about?
是我的…哦 兄弟
What's my... Oh brother.
嗯 这个 呃——这很难总结
Well it's uh...it's difficult to summarize.
呒…
Um...
开始是一种第一人称叙述…
it starts out as a kind offirst - person narrative...
一个男人照顾他中风后的父亲
about a guy taking careof his father after a stroke.
- 哦 - 这个有点根据我的个人经历
- Oh. - It's kind of based on uh personal experience.
不过只是…只是大体上
But only... only loosely.
小说名字叫什么?
What's the title?
昨天的明天
The Day After Yesterday.
哦 你是说今天
Oh. You mean today.
呃…呃 是的我是说 对不过没那么简单…
Um... uh yeah.I mean r - right. But it's more...
是不是关于 比如 死亡和永恒 或者…
So it's about like death and mortality or...
哦 对…
[Sighs] Uh yeah...
对 不过也不全是
Y... Not really.
我 哦…用了很多跳跃式结构
I uh... It de... It jumps around a lot.
这是我想表达的 从某种意义上你懂我的意思么?
That's what it's about in a way.You know what I mean?
你开始以父亲的眼光看周围的一切
You start to see everythingfrom the point of view of the father.
并且 呃 同时有很多其他事情发生了…并列叙述
And uh a lot of other things happen...parallel narratives.
有点乱
[Laughs] It's kind of a mess.
然后 最终整个事情向前发展…
And then eventually the whole thing sort of evolves...
或者衰退…
or devolves...
最后成为一种格里耶式的谜
into this sort ofRobbe - Grillet mystery.
你明白么?
You know?
但是没有真正的答案
But no real resolution.
- 喔 - 这个…
- Wow. - [Chuckles] It...
嗯我觉得你能出版它真是太棒了
Well I think it's really greatyou're getting it published.
真的我是说 我知道仅仅把它写出来就很难了
Really. I mean I know how hard it isjust to write it even.
是啊
Yeah.
我是说 像我 我的论文星期五就要交了…
I mean like me I've got this paperdue on Friday...
我紧张的一塌糊涂 像高中生一样
and I'm freaked out about it just like in high school.
- 论文 嗯? - 对
- A paper huh? - Yeah.
我正在读园艺学的硕士学位
I'm going for a master's degreein horticulture.
慢慢啃的
Sorta chipping away on it.
- 园艺学? 真的? - 唔
- Horticulture? Really? - Mmm.
我都不知道这附近还有大学
I didn't even knowthat there was a college here.
噢 我跑通勤到圣路易斯奥比斯波 两周一次
Well I commute to San Luis Obispotwice a week.
园艺学? 喔
Horticulture? Wow.
那你是想在酿酒园还是什么地方工作?
So do you want to workin a winery or something?
可能吧
Maybe.
噢
Oh.
呒
Hmm.
那 我什么时候才能读你的书?
So when can I read your book?
嗯 我…你知道 我正好有手稿在车里
Well I... You know I... Well I do happento have a manuscript in my car.
呃 还没有校对过…
Um it's not proofed or anything...
所以会有很多书写错误
so it's... it's full of typos.
- 如果你不介意书写错误… - 不介意 谁管呀?
- If you don't mind typos... Oh no. Who cares?
我可是错别字大王
I'm the queen of typos.
好的
Okay.
呒
Mmm.
啊
Ahh.
能问你个私人问题么 迈尔斯?
You know can I ask youa personal question Miles?
当然
Sure.
你为什么那么喜欢皮诺?
Why are you so into pinot?
我的意思是 就好像你的一个特征一样
- [Laughing] - I mean it's like a thing with you.
呃…我也不知道 我也不知道
Uh... I don't know. I don't know.
呃…只是一种很难种植的葡萄
Um... it's a hard grape to grow.
你应该知道 对吧?
As you know. Right?
它 呃 它皮很薄…
It's uh... It's thin - skinned...
喜怒无常 熟得很早
temperamental ripens early.
它…你知道 它很难生存…
It's... You know it's not a survivor...
不像卡博耐(cabernet)…
like cabernet...
可以在任何地方生长…
which can just grow anywhere...
甚至没人管也能兴旺
and thrive even when it's neglected.
不行 皮诺需要持久的关心和照料你知道?
No pinot needs constant careand attention. You know?
其实 它只能长在…
And in fact it can only grow...
那些极特别的地方世界很少的几个角落
in these really specific little tucked - away corners of the world.
只有…只有…
And... And only...
最耐心最精心的种植者
the most patientand nurturing of growers...
才能种它 真的
can do it really.
只有那些真正愿意花时间的人…
Only somebodywho really takes the time...
真正理解皮诺潜力的人…
to understand pinot's potential...
才能引导它进入全盛阶段
can then coax itinto its fullest expression.
然后呢? 我是指…
And then? I mean...
哦 它的香味儿 是最持久最辉煌的…
Oh its flavors they're justthe most haunting and brilliant...
最震撼最微妙的…
and thrilling and subtle and...
最古老的 在整个星球上
ancient on the planet.
我是说 你知道 卡博耐也能很强健很显耀…
No I mean you know cabernetscan be powerful and exalting too...
但它们对我来说太平凡了 因为某种原因 相对而言
but they seem prosaic to me for some reason by comparison.
我不知道 我不知道
- [Laughing] - I don't know. I don't know.
你觉得呢?
What about you?
我觉得什么?
What about me?
不知道你为什么对葡萄酒着迷?
I don't know.Why are you into wine?
噢 我…我想 我…
Oh I... I think I...
- 我最初对酒着迷是因为我的前夫 - 啊
- I originally got into wine through my ex - husband. - Ah.
你知道 他有一个很大的值得炫耀的酒窖
You know he had this bigsort of show - off cellar.
- 明白么? - 对
- You know? - Right.
- 然后我发现我的味觉非常敏锐 - 嗯哼
- But then I discovered thatI had a really sharp palate. - Mm - hmm.
我喝的越多…
And the more I drank...
我就越喜欢它使我产生的思想
the more I likedwhat it made me think about.
比方说?
Like what?
比方说我意识到他是一个骗子
Like what a fraud he was.
喔
[Laughs] Wow.
不 我的意思是 我喜欢去思考酒的生命
No I mean I like to thinkabout the life of wine.
嗯
Yeah.
它是一种怎样一种有生命的东西
How it's a living thing.
我喜欢思考…
I like to think about...
在葡萄成熟的一年里会发生什么…
what was going on the yearthe grapes were growing...
太阳是怎样照耀的…
how the sun was shining...
在下雨的时候
if it rained.
我喜欢思考…
I like to think about...
那些照顾和采摘葡萄的人们…
all the people who tendedand picked the grapes...
如果是陈年的酒的话 有多少人现在已经不在人世了
and if it's an old wine how many of them must be dead by now.
我喜欢葡萄酒在不停的进化
I like how wine continues to evolve.
好比 如果我今天打开一瓶酒的话…
Like if I opened a bottle of wine today...
它的味道会不同与我在其他日子打开它
it would taste different than ifI'd opened it on any other day.
因为一瓶酒其实是有生命的…
Because a bottle of wineis actually alive...
而且它不停的进化 不停的得到新的元素
and it's constantly evolvingand gaining complexity.
这样 直到它的顶峰…
That is until it peaks...
就像你那瓶61年的酒
like your '61 .
然后它开始了平稳的…
And then it begins its steady...
不可避免的衰退
inevitable decline.
嗯
Hmm.
它的口味变的真他妈的好
And it tastes so fucking good.
嗯
Yeah.
不过你知道 我…我 呃…
But you know I... I uh...
我还喜欢皮诺以外的其他葡萄酒
I like other wines besides pinot too.
我是说 最近我开始非常喜欢雷斯林(Rieslings)
I mean latelyI've been really into Rieslings.
你喜欢雷斯林? 雷斯林?
You like Rieslings? Rieslings?
嗯哼
Mm - hmm.
这后面有洗手间么?
There's a bathroom in the back?
- 有 穿过厨房就是 - 我马上回来
- Yeah. It's through the kitchen. - I'll be right back.
上帝 你他妈的衰人
[Exhales] God you are such a fuckin' loser.
你真他妈让我恶心
You make me so fuckin' sick.
噢 上帝啊 来吧
[Groaning] Oh God. Ah come on.
嗨
Hi.
- 我过来拿点水 - 嗯
- I was just getting some water. - Okay.
- 你要水么? - 不
- You want some water? - No.
好了现在已经很晚了
Okay. It's getting kind of late.
我真的得走了
I should really go.
你知道去"风车"该怎么走吧? 两个右转再一个左转
So you know how to get to the Windmill?Two rights and a left.
- 知道了 - 好的
- Got it. - Okay.
我晚上过的很愉快 迈尔斯 真的
I had a nice time tonight Miles.I really did.
好我也是
Good. So did I.
- 那好吧 再会了 - 呃…
- Okay. Well I'll see you around then. - Um...
你还想看我的小说么?
Did you still want to read my novel?
噢 是的 当然
Oh yeah. Of course.
[嘀咕]
[Groans]
是的
Yeah.
- 太好了 - 等一下
- Great. - Just a sec.
- 给 - 噢 喔
- Here. - Oh wow.
我希望你喜欢
Well I hope you like it.
你什么时候看不下去了就别看了 我不会生气的
And feel free to stop reading it any time.I will not be offended.
好
Okay.
- 那 晚安 迈尔斯 - 晚安
- Well good night Miles. - Good night.
哦 靠
Oh fuck.
[Groans] Oh fuck.
那个妞真他妈的难以置信 伙计难以置信!
That fucking chick is unbelievable dude.Unbelievable!
喔!
Whoo! Boy.
哦 她可真下流 迈尔斯
Ohh she is nasty Miles.
下流 下流 下流!
Nasty nasty nasty.!
- 嗯 我很高兴你终于发泄了 - 是啊 哥们
- Well I'm glad you got it out of your system. - Yeah baby.
恭喜你任务完成了
Congratulations.Mission accomplished.
哦 嗨 迈尔斯!
Oh hi Miles!
嗨!
Hi.
嘿 你不会请了斯蒂芬妮和我们一起去吧?
- [Toilet Flushing] - Hey you didn't invite Stephanieto come with us did you?
哦 听着 伙计 计划有变了斯蒂芬妮今天不上班
Oh listen man. Change of plans.Stephanie's off today
所以 你看 我想和她去爬山
so you know I'm thinkin' about goin' on a hike.
我们本来今天要去打高尔夫的
We were supposed to play golf.
你觉得怎么样? 你自己去 伙计你自己去事实上 你可以用我的会员卡
You know what? You go man.You go. In fact use my clubs.
会员卡都是全新的是克莉丝汀她爸送给我的礼物
- They're brand - new.They were a gift from Christine's dad. - [Disgusted Sigh]
给 我请客就用这个
Here I'll pay for it. Right there.
等晚一些时候 我们三个可以一起去The Hitching Post
And then later the three of us we can go to The Hitching Post.
我们可以坐在玛雅的餐桌那儿
We could sit at one of Maya's tables.
她会给我们拿些好酒 知道么?
She'll bring us some great wine you know?
然后我们四个可以干点什么不 我不要
- Then the four of us will do something. - No. Count me out.
哦 我明白了
Oh I see.
昨天晚上不是很顺利 嗯? 真是吃惊啊
Didn't go so great last night huh?What a shocker.
你是说喝醉了给维多利亚打电话并没有使你进入状态?
You mean getting drunk and callingVictoria didn't put you in the mood?
妈的傻瓜
Dumb fuck.
晚上见 伙计是的 不过也许你应该先查一下你的短信
- Later man. - Yeah well maybe you shouldcheck your messages first.
哦 天哪
- [Escalating Tones] - Oh boy.
是的 她在这里也留言了
Yeah she's been leavingmessages here too.
嗯好的
Yeah. Okay.
你应该给她打电话我会的再见
- You should call her. - I will. I'll see you.
现在就打!好吧靠!
- Right now! - Okay. Fuck!
你是谁呀? 我妈? 随便
- What are you my mom? - Well.
你不介意到外面等吧?
Would you mind waiting outside?
昨天晚上过的很好是啊吃的东西不错
- That was fun last night. - Yeah. Good food.
嘿 我 - 我早上和玛雅谈过了她说她昨天晚上也很开心
Hey I - I talked to Maya this morning.She said she had a fun time too.
你应该给她打电话
You should call her.
杰克在哪儿? 呃 他得打个电话
- Where's Jack? - Uh had to make a phone call.
哦
Oh.
迈尔斯 迈尔斯
Miles. Miles.
嘿 伙计 呃 上次那个安全套你还有没有了?
Hey man uh do you havethat other condom?
在我外套里
In my jacket.
克莉丝汀怎么说?
What did uh Christine say?
很侥幸用语音留言了一切都没问题
Lucked out. Got voice mail.Everything's cool.
哈哈 我来了嗨!
- Ha ha.! Here I am. - [Stephanie] Hi.!
好了么? 好了
- Ready? - Yeah.
重型炮弹!
Cannonball!
请输入您的密码并按井号键
[Female Voice Electronic] Please dial your password and press pound.
目前您没有留言
You have no messages at this time.
发送消息 请按2…
To send a message press 2...
- 啊…
- [Moaning Panting] - Uh...
不要现在进来!
Not now. Not now!
好
- Yeah. - [Stephanie Grunting]
嘿 你来了
Hey there you are.
是的嘿 伙计
- Yup. - Hey man.
你在喝什么?
What are you drinking?
好不好喝?
Is it any good?
我能不能 能不能来一杯?
Can... Can I get a glass please?
谢谢
Thanks.
斯蒂芬妮今天带我去皮诺种植地了 迈尔斯
Stephanie took me outto the pinot fields today Miles.
上帝 真是美啊
God it was so awesome.
我觉得我已经对整个过程摸出些门道来了
I think I'm really starting to geta handle on the whole process.
从土壤到藤蔓 还有…你们怎么说的来着…
The soil to the vine and the...what do you call it?
从选种到收获
The selection to the harvest.
就是他们用那个很大的容器搅拌葡萄?
Then that thing they do withthe big containers where they mix it?
真是太棒了 整个过程
It's really neat the whole thing.
我们还从葡萄藤上摘了皮诺葡萄吃
Then we ate pinot grapesright off the vine.
有点酸…
They were a little sour...
不过表现出出色的构造潜力…
but showing excellent potentialfor structure...
从头至尾 我认为
down the line I think.
斯蒂芬妮 伙计 她可真懂行
Stephanie man.She really knows her shit.
嗯斯蒂芬妮在哪儿?
Hmm. Where is Stephanie?
呃 她在楼上清理清理
Uh she's upstairs cleaning up.
你他妈的到底在干嘛?
What the fuck are you doing?
什么? 和那个妞
- What? - With this chick.
怎么了?
What?
她知不知道星期六的事?
Does she know about Saturday?
哦 不知道吧不过我对她是诚实的
Well not exactly.I've been honest with her.
我并没有告诉她我是单身啊
I haven't told her I'm available.
她知道我们这趟旅行只有几天
She knows this tripis only for a few days.
再说 我…
Besides I just...
再说什么? 我…嗯 你知道…
- Besides what? - I'm... Well you know...
婚礼怎么了?
- The wedding. - What?
我正在考虑
I... I've just been doingsome thinking about it.
哦 你在考虑了然后呢?
Oh you've been thinking. And?
也许我想把婚礼推迟一下 就这样
Might have to putthe wedding on hold is all.
你看 我知道这个很难…
Look I know thatthat could be tricky...
很难让人一开始就接受嗯
- for certain people to accept at first. - Yeah.
是吧? 不过人生很短 迈尔斯
All right?But life is short Miles.
我必须在做出这样一个重大决定前确定自己这样做是正确的
I have to be sure I'm doing the right thingbefore taking such a big step.
你知道么? 这也不是光光为了我自己
You know what?That's not just for my sake.
我也是为克莉丝汀的感情着想
I'm looking outfor Christine's feelings too.
我是说 和斯蒂芬妮在一起让我大开眼界
I mean being with Stephaniehas completely opened my eyes.
她不保守 没有控制欲 她很棒
She's not uptight or controlling.She's just cool.
我是说 她闻起来是不一样的 她尝起来是不一样的
I mean she smells different she tastes different.
她操起来也是不一样的好吧
- She fucks different. - Okay.
她操起来象个动物
She fucks like an animal.
我得告诉你 伙计
I gotta tell you man.
我昨天晚上插的很深
I went deep last night.
很深
Deep.
我原以为我可以从你这儿得到些理解 看来我得不到了
I thought I'd get a little understandingfrom you but I'm not gonna get that.
理解什么 杰克?
Understanding about what Jack?
我可能爱上另一个女人了
- I might be in love with another woman. - [Laughs]
爱上? 真的?
In love? Really?
和一个倒酒的女人呆24个小时 你就他妈的爱上她了?
Twenty - four hours with some wine - pourerchick and you're fuckin' in love.
算了吧!你愿意失去一切么?
Come on! And you're gonnagive up everything?
我是这样想的
Here's what I'm thinkin'.
你和我 我们搬到这附近 买一片葡萄园
You and me we move up here we buy a vineyard.
你设计葡萄酒 我来处理生意方面
You design the wine.I'll handle the business side.
你得到了灵感 没准儿能写另一部小说 一本有市场的
You get inspired maybe writeanother novel one that can sell.
哦 上帝啊不会吧
Oh my God. No no.
对我来说 如果有试演 洛杉矶就在附近 伙计
As for me if an audition comes up L.A.'s right there man.
就两个小时的路 可能还不到上帝 你疯了
- It's two hours away. Not even. - Jesus Christ. You're crazy.
你已经疯了
You've gone crazy.
我只知道我是个演员
All I know is that I'm an actor.
直觉对我最重要
All I have is my instinct.
你现在让我违背我的直觉
You're asking me to go against it.
嗨 你们好
[Stephanie] Hi guys.!
嗨 嗨
Hi. Hi.
我们可能该走了是的
- We should probably get going. - Yeah.
去哪儿?
Where?
我知道开车的人都去哪儿
I know where all the drivers go.
嗯? 好吧困难的部分来了来吧好
Huh? All right. Here comes the tricky part.There you go. Nice.
好好的 这儿有个桥
Nice. Okay it's the bridge.
金门大桥来吧
Golden Gate Bridge. There you go.
你知道 有件事…我是说 其实我也经不太在乎了你知道我的意思么?
You know it's a thing... I mean I've gotten over it. You know what I mean?
嗯哼斯蒂芬妮已经听过上千次了…
- Mm - hmm. - Stephanie's heard this a thousand times...
如果我是在圣玛丽长大的 如果我有机会
but if I'd bought up in Santa Mariawhen I had a chance...
我可以赚一大笔钱 就是他们在建那个 呃…
I would've made a fortunewhen they put in that uh...
- 家得宝家居 - 家得宝家居
- Home Depot. - Home Depot.
那些商店呀你爸爸也知道这些
And those stores.And your father knew about it too.
他可真他妈是个胆小鬼
He's such a fuckin' chickenshit.
总是那样就是他妈的胆小鬼
Always was.Just a fuckin'chickenshit.
什么都害怕
- Just too scared. - [Coughing]
这个惹你烦了么? 有没有? 没关系 没关系
- Is this bothering you? You sure? - It's fine. Yeah.
嘿 伙计我得确保锡耶纳 和 斯蒂芬妮安全到家
Hey man. I'm gonna just make surethat Siena and Stephanie get home safe.
好的好也许我俩可以晚点再会面
- Okay. - All right. Maybe we'll hook up with you later.
当然随便也许我可以去看个电影什么的
Sure. Whatever. Maybe I'llgo catch a movie or something.
再见 迈尔斯 - 谢谢 斯蒂芬妮 再见
- See you later Miles. - Thanks Stephanie. See you.
- 再见 锡耶纳 - 再见
- Bye Siena. - Bye.
- 卡里尔 很高兴认识你 - 我很喜欢和你聊天
- Caryl very nice meeting you. - I loved talking with you.
谢谢如果你要出去 打我手机
- Thanks. - If you go out later call me on my cell.
好!
[High - pitched Voice] Okay!
好是这个么? 是的
- Okay. That's it? - Yeah.
还有 请给我拿一期Barely Legal?
Actually could I get a uh...a Barely Legal please?
谢谢不 是…对不起 要新的一期
Thank you. No actually...Sorry. The new one.
好的
Okay.
谢谢
Thanks.
什么…哦
What... Oh.
嗨 迈尔斯 玩的怎么样? 嗨
- Hey Miles. How's it hanging? - Hey.
哦 你了解我我喜欢这里
Oh you know me. I love it up here.
你怎么样? 星期二晚上很忙
- How 'bout you? - Busy for a Tuesday night.
有一车老年人来葡萄酒之旅
We had a busload of old folkson a wine tour.
平时他们也不是很吵闹的但今晚有点奇怪
Usually they're not too rowdy but tonight something was going on.
我也不知道 没准是满月的原因你想要点什么?
I don't know. A full moon or something.Anyway what can I get you?
- Highliner 杯装的还是瓶装的?
- Highliner. - Glass or bottle?
瓶的好的
- Bottle. - You got it.
哎 呃 玛雅还在工作么?
Say is uh Maya working?
玛雅? 嗯…有 我没看见她
Maya? Uh no I haven't seen her.
我想她今晚调休
I think she's off tonight.
你还好吧 迈尔斯? 是的 我还好
- You okay Miles? - Yeah I'm good.
啊 妈的
Ah crap.
你昨天晚上见到玛雅了么? 没有
- Did you ever get ahold of Maya yesterday? - Nope.
嗯? 没有
- Hmm? - No.
她很喜欢你 伙计斯蒂芬妮会告诉你的
She really likes you man.Stephanie'll tell you.
你能不能给我点地方? 好的
- Could you just give me a little room? Please? - Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
生活中 有时你得趁热打铁趁热打铁
In life you gotta strikewhile the iron's hot. Iron is hot.
明智的建议 杰克
Sage advice Jack.
现在 记住 脚后跟站稳嗯哼
- Now remember sit back on your heels. - Mm - hmm.
好了么? 转腹部
All right?Turn through the abdomen.
腹部
Abdomen.
哦 给点尖叫…很好
- [Grunts] Oh for cryin'... Nice.
你的经纪人怎么样了? 有信儿了么?
[Jack] What about your agent?You hear anything yet?
没有你觉得会有什么事?
- [Miles] Nope. - What do you think's going on?
什么事都可能你检查你的留言了么?
- Could be anything. - You been checking your messages?
不停的查嗯
- Obsessively. - Huh.
看来我得接受我又浪费了生命中的三年
Guess I'll just have to learn to kiss offanother three years of my life.
但是你还没有得到任何消息呢…
But you haven't heard anything yet...
你不觉得你的消极论断还为时过早么?
so don't you think your negativity'sa little premature?
呒 好的 你知道操他的纽约出版商
Hmm? All right. You know fuck the New York publishers.
你自己出版 迈尔斯 我入股
Publish it yourself Miles.I'll chip in.
把它出版了 找人写评论
Just get it out there.Get it reviewed.
放在图书馆里 让公众决定
Get it in libraries.Let the public decide.
不要打在表面上
Don't come over the top.
保持不动闭嘴
- Stay still. - Shut up.
保持不动最重要
It's all about stillness.
内心的平静闭嘴 闭嘴 闭嘴!
- Inner quiet. - Shut up. Shut up. Shut up!
上帝呀 你到底哪根筋搭错了?
Jesus Christ man!What the hell is wrong with you?
求求你了 就闭嘴吧!靠!
Please just shut up! Fuck!
上帝啊你这么冲干吗 伙计?
- God. - What's with the hostility man?
我知道你目前的生活有些挫折…
I know you're a little frustratedwith your life right now...
不过你可以选择不那么敌视
- but you can choose to be less hostile. - [Chuckling]
那个混蛋打到我们这里来了
The fucker hit into us.
快点 行不?
[Shouting] Hurry it up will ya?
哦 哦
Oh boy. Oh boy.
嘿 这样不好 笨蛋!
Hey that's not cool asshole!
好球笨蛋们
[Jack] Nice shot.Jackoffs.
你到底在干什么? 哎呀 小心
- What the hell are you doing? - Oops. Look out.
嗯? 呃 - 哼
Uh? Uh - huh.
哦 哦 看 看
Oh. Oh check it out.
好戏来了 好戏来了开过去
- This is gonna be fun. This is gonna be fun. - Go to it.
不要放弃玛雅 像她那样又酷又聪明的女人需要恒心
Just don't give up on Maya. Cool smartchicks like that require persistence.
我不想谈这个了 求你了
I don't wanna talk about it please.
我只知道她很美 精神丰富
All I know is that she's beautiful a lot of soul.
她对你非常合适
She's perfect for you.
如果看不见你们两个在一起我这周不会好过的
I'm just not gonna feel good about this weekuntil I know you guys have hooked up.
你难道不想要那种温暖的小盒子加紧你的小弟弟的感觉么?
Don't you want to feel that cozy little boxgrip down on your johnson?
嘿!往后想想 伙计?
Hey! Mind keeping it down buddy?
当这个女人发现我是怎样生活的…
A woman finds out how I live...
我并不是一个出版作家 我根本就是个骗子…
that I'm not a published author that I'm a liar essentially...
她所有的兴趣就会很快消失掉
any interest she hasis gonna evaporate real quick.
如果你到了我这个年龄还没有钱 就意味着你连游戏的资格都没有了
If you don't have money at my age you're not even in the game anymore.
你只是一个等在abattoir(法语)里的牲畜
You're just a pasture animalwaiting for the abattoir.
- Abattoir 什么意思? - 屠宰场
- Abattoir. What is that? - Slaughterhouse.
屠宰场 嗯 不过你知道么?
Abattoir. Huh.But you know what?
你会成为一个出版作家…
You are gonna bea published author...
因为这个星期你就要听到关于你的书的好消息了
because you're gonna get the good newsthis week about your book.
我知道你会的 我可以感觉到
- I know you are. I can feel it. - # [Cell Phone Chiming]
嗯 斯蒂芬妮
Huh. Stephanie.
嗨 宝贝儿 是的
Hey honey. Yeah.
是的 是的
Yeah. Yeah.
太好了!
Yeah!
嗨嗨
- Hey. - [Jack] Hi.
嗨 迈尔斯 我听说你昨晚到餐厅去找我了
Hey Miles. I heard you stopped bythe restaurant to see me last night.
哦 是的不 我是说 呃 是的
Oh yeah. No. I mean uh yeah.
我去那里喝了一杯不过没看见你
I stopped by for a drink.I didn't see you.
我去上课了哦
- I had class. - Oh.
那 很高兴现在见到你
Well nice to see you now.
我也很高兴见到你
It's good to see you too.
席拉酒
- [Miles] Syrah. - [All Chattering]
圣巴巴拉周围最古老的席拉葡萄
[Miles] Oldest Syrah grapesin Santa Barbara County.
你知道么?
Did you know that?
你不知道么?
You didn't know that?
黑皮诺葡萄最早开始种植可能是
[Man] The pinot noir grapehas been cultivated perhaps...
从古代勃艮第
since antiquity in Burgundy.
正是这种精确的…
And it is precisely this ancient...
从远古继承的酿酒知识…
and inherited winemakingknowledge...
促成了它的成功
that has contributed to its success.
我在那里数着 16 17真的?
- I was like 1 6 1 7. - Really?
是啊 快枯燥死了!
Yeah. I'm gonna die!
哦 天哪 乱七八糟的妈妈?
- Oh God. What a drag. - Mom?
哦哦 嘿 嗨
- Oh. - Oh hey. Hi.
是不是太吵了?
- Is it too loud? - [Coughing]
对不起哦 杰克叔叔带你上床睡觉
Sorry. Oh UncleJackwill put you back to bed.
过来 小朋友哦!
Come here little sister. Ooh!
我们会安静一点的 好不好?
We'll be more quiet okay?
晚安抱歉非常抱歉
- Good night. I'm sorry. - I'm so sorry.
我最喜欢的 冰淇淋是…
- My favorite as far as ice cream... [Coughing]
- 胖猴子奶昔
- [Maya] Chunky Monkey.!
你们今天应该到我们餐厅吃午饭
You guys should come bythe restaurant for lunch today.
很好我们最晚可以什么时候到? 大概2:30
- Great. What's the latest we can get there? - About 2:30.
你有没有听说圣巴巴拉有个波尔多酒品尝大会…
Did you hear about this Bordeauxtasting dinner down in Santa Barbara...
在这个周六晚上?
on Saturday night?
有点贵 不过你如果愿意去的话 我也去
It's kind of pricey but if you wanted to go I'd be into it.
你们为什么不能过了这个周末再走?
Why don't you just stayfor the weekend?
不行 我们必须得星期五回去排演晚餐?
No we have to get back Fridayfor the rehearsal dinner.
为什么要排演晚餐?
What rehearsal dinner?
有人要结婚了么?
Who's getting married?
你是不是根本什么都不打算说? 我当然打算告诉你的
- Were you ever gonna say anything? - Yes of course I was.
就刚才 我本来可以编个故事骗你 但我没有
Just now I could've told yousome story but I didn't.
我已经说实话了 玛雅!别碰我!
- I told you the truth. Maya! - Don't touch me!
送我回家
Just take me home.
你知不知道他对她都说了些什么?
Do you have any ideawhat he's been saying to her?
他是个演员 所以不会是什么好话只是说他又多爱她
- He's an actor so it can't be good. - Only that he loves her.
她是唯一一个震撼他世界的女人 他多么喜欢锡耶纳…
How she's the only woman that's everrocked his world how he adores Siena...
他多么想搬到这儿来 买个地方和她俩住一起 他可以跑通勤
how he wants to move here andget a place with the two of themand commute when he has to.
我肯定他自己都以为自己说的每个字都是真的呢
I'm sure he believed every word of it.
请相信我
Please believe me.
我昨晚差一点就要告诉你真相了 不过…
I was on the vergeof telling you last night but...
不过你想先操我
But you wanted to fuck me first.
不 玛雅不是的
Oh Maya. No.
是的
Yeah.
你知道 我刚刚用了3年的时间…
You know I've just spentthe last three years of my life...
试着从一场充满欺骗的婚姻里解脱出来…
trying to extricate myself froma relationship that was full of deception...
我刚刚开始感觉好点
and I'm doing just fine.
我离婚以后没有和任何人在一起过…
And I haven't been with anybodysince my divorce...
这对我是非常重要事 玛雅
so this has been a big deal for me Maya.
和你度过的时光 呃…还有昨天晚上
Hanging out with you and uh...and last night.
我是真的喜欢你 玛雅…
I really like you Maya...
而且我并不像杰克
and I am notJack.
我是…我是…
I'm... I'm...
在圣地亚哥州立时我是他的大一室友
[Sighs] I'm his freshman year roommatefrom San Diego State.
我的好孩子回来了!
- [Door Closes] - There's my boy!
他回来了你爸爸是谁呀?
There he is.But who's your daddy?
你爸爸是谁呀? 哦!杰克 算了吧
- Who is your daddy? Oh! - Jack come on.
哦 让我来爱你吧放开噢
- Oh let me love you. - Let go. Oh!
放下我 杰克
- Let me down Jack. - [Laughing]
我真替你骄傲啊 呒 呒
I am so proud of you.Ah. Mmm. Mmm.
嗯 非常好好了 好了 告诉我细节
- Well that's nice. - Okay. All right. Details.
我喜欢听细节不
- I love details. - No.
什么? 上帝 那是隐私
- What? - Jesus. It's private.
你最好把经过告诉我不然 我要把你的小弟弟打个结
You better tell me what happened or I'll tie your dick in a knot.
我们就走吧 行不行?
Let's just leave it okay?
你根本就没干 是不是?
- You didn't get any did you? - [Sighs]
你是个同性恋是的 对了对 我是同性恋
- You're a homo. - Yeah right. Yup I'm a homo.
是的 是的
Yeah. Yeah.
随便你乱想的就是经过
Just make up whatever you want and that's what happened.
把我的同性恋自白书写下来 我会在上面签字的
Write out my gay confession and I'll sign it.
好不好? 不要老是逼我
Okay? Just stop pushing meall the time.
你是个婴儿 杰克
You're an infant Jack.
整个世界对你就是个大派对…好了
- This is all a big party for you... - Okay.
但对我不是行了
- but not for me. - Come on.
对不起 伙计
I'm sorry man.
你是不是假装的时候有困难?
Did you have trouble performing?
是的 就是这个原因
- Yeah that's it. - [Phone Rings]
- 不要接
- Don't answer it. - [Rings]
不要接
Don't answer it.
- 杰克 - 喂
- Jack. - Hello.
是的
[Chuckling] Yeah.
呃 - 呃是克莉丝汀
Uh - huh. [Whispers] It's Christine.
是的 是的呃 - 呃
Yeah. Yeah. Uh - huh.
嘿 我回来马上给你打电话
Hey let me call you right back.
迈尔斯和我正有事
Miles and I are kindain the middle of something.
没有 没什么重要的 就是…他又开始行为反常了是的
Nah it's nothing serious.Just...He's having one ofhis freak - outs. Yeah.
我也爱你 我等下打给你
- # [Dance: Woman Singing] - I love you too. I'll call you back.
整个星期已经变味儿了这不是我们本来想要的
[Miles] This whole week has gone sour.It hasn't gone the way it was supposed to.
我想在只想回家
I just want to go home.
我知道你的需要
I know what you need.
这个怎么样? 我们还没有喝过这里的呢
[Jack] How 'bout this one?We didn't hit this one.
- Frass Canyon 笑话吧 你原来来过这里?
- Frass Canyon. It's a joke. - You ever actually been in there?
用不着来这儿我说我们还是尝尝吧 都已经来了
- I don't have to. - I say we check it out. We're right here.
它的味道就像他妈洛杉矶校车的屁股
[Miles] It tastes like the backof a fucking L.A. school bus.
嗯 他们可能没有去梗…
Now they probably didn't de - stem...
想假装酒的浓度很高
hoping for some semblanceof concentration.
把它和叶子和老鼠一起碾碎…
Crushed it up with leaves and mice...
再配上腐臭的焦油和松脂漱口水这些烂东西
and then wound up with this rancid tarand turpentine mouthwash bullshit.
他妈的骗人
Fuckin' Raid.
我觉得味道挺好
Tastes pretty good to me.
嗯对了他们有一种保留的皮诺
Hmm. Look.They have a reserve pinot.
- 我用下你的电话 - 怎么了?
- Let me use your phone. - What's up?
- 我不能再等下去了 我要给伊芙琳打电话 - 好的
- I can't take it anymore. I gotta call Evelyn. - Okay.
伊芙琳·伯曼 - 西尔弗曼 的办公室
[Woman] Evelyn Berman - Silverman's office.
- 嗨  詹妮弗 还是我 迈尔斯 噢 嗨 迈尔斯
- Hi Jennifer. It's Miles again. - Oh hi Miles.
嗨我看看能不能接通她
- Hi. - Let me see if I can get her.
好的
Okay.
你很幸运我给你接过去好的
- You're in luck. I'll put you through. - Okay.
- 嗨 迈尔斯 - 嗨  伊夫林
- Hi Miles. - Hi Evelyn.
是你最受宠的客户
It's your favorite client. [Chuckles]
你的旅行怎么样? 噢 很好 很好
- How's the trip? - Oh it's good it's good.
你知道 我们就喝喝酒放松放松
You know we're drinkingsome good wines kicking back.
非常好是的
- It's very nice. - Right.
怎么样了? 还是没有回音 嗯?
So what's happening?There's still no word huh?
嗯 事实上 已经有消息了
Well actually there is word.
我早上和基思•库兹曼通过话了
I spoke to Keith Kurtzmanthis morning.
嗯怎么样?
Right. And?
嗯…他们没有通过
And... they're passing.
"迷题"出版社没有通过 他说他们很喜欢你的小说
Conundrum's passing.He said they really liked it.
他们非常希望能出版它 但是他们不知道怎么推销它
They really wanted to do it but they justcouldn't figure out how to market it.
他说很难有市场
He said it was a really tough call.
噢 是的
Oh. Right.
很遗憾 迈尔斯
- I'm sorry Miles. - [Sighs]
我不知道我们还能怎么办
So I don't know where that leaves us.
我不知道继续投稿还有多少意义
I'm not sure how much more mileageI can get out of continuing to submit it.
我想这就是目前出版业不景气的一个不幸的例子吧…
I think it's one of those unfortunate casesin the business right now...
一本出色的书却找不到归宿
a - a fabulous book with no home.
整个出版业都已经没有勇气了
[Evelyn's Voice] The whole industry's gotten gutless.
并不是说你的书不好
It's not about the qualityof the books anymore.
只是市场的问题
It's only about the marketing.
- 打搅一下 能不能给我 呃 - 倒在这里? - 当然
- Excuse me. Could I geta uh pour down here please? - Sure.
这一点上席拉酒有点特别
There's a uh specialon the Syrah by the case.
再给我倒上
Hit me again.
谢谢
Thanks.
对不起 你能不能给我倒满?
Excuse me.Could you just pour me a full glass?
我会付钱的 好不好?
I'll pay for it okay?
先生 这里是酿酒园 不是酒吧
Sir this is a winery not a bar.
噢 得了吧
Oh. Come on.
就他妈给我满上一杯
Just give me a full goddamn pour.
对不起
Excuse me.
你为什么不买上一瓶 出去喝呢?
Why don't you buy a bottle then go outside?
- 你要干什么? - 我给你讲了 我要喝一杯 看来我只好自己动手了
- What are you doing? - I told you I need a drink so I'm going to help myself.
- 哼 哥们 你想怎么着? - 放下杯子
- Okay pal? What do you think? - Put the glass down.
放下他妈的杯子 操!
Let go of the fucking glass fucker!
呒
- [Groaning] - Mmm.
就这么着噢 哦 哦 哦 伙计 哦 伙计
- That's that. - Ho ho ho ho ho. Ho buddy. Ho buddy.
没关系把他带出去
- It's okay. - Get him out ofhere.
多谢没关系他 呃…他妈妈刚死了
- Thanks a lot! - It's okay. His uh... His mother just died.
你可以再写一部你有很多好点子 对吧?
So you'll write another one.You've got lots of ideas right?
没了 江郎才尽了我就不是个作家
No I'm finished. I'm not a writer.
我只是个中学英语老师
I'm a middle school English teacher.
啊 整个世界都不会在乎我想说什么
Ah the world doesn't give a shitwhat I have to say.
我的存在是没必要的
I'm unnecessary. [Chuckles]
我是那么的不重要 连自杀都不行
I'm so insignificant I can't even kill myself.
迈尔斯 这到底是什么意思?
Miles what the hellis that supposed to mean?
行了 伙计 你知道
Come on man. You know.
海明威 塞克斯汀 普拉斯 沃尔夫
Hemingway Sexton Plath Woolf.
你不能书都没有出版就自杀
You can't kill yourselfbefore you've even been published.
那写《傻瓜同盟》的那个家伙呢?
- [Sighs] - What about the guy that wroteConfederacy Of Dunces?
他在书出版之前就自杀了看他现在多出名
He committed suicide before hewas published. Look how famous he is.
谢谢
Thanks.
别放弃 好么? 你一定会成功的
Just don't give up. All right?You're gonna make it.
前半生已经过去了…
Half my life is over...
我却没什么可展示的 什么都没有
and I have nothingto show for it nothing.
我是摩天大楼窗户上的一个指印
I'm a thumbprinton the window of a skyscraper.
我是擦大便手纸上的一粒粪渣…
I'm a smudge of excrementon a tissue...
和成千上万的下水道污秽一起奔向大海
surging out to seawith a million tons of raw sewage.
看到么? 这就是
See? Right there.
就你刚才说的? 就很美
Just what you just said?That is beautiful.
"一粒粪渣奔向大海"
"A smudge of excrementsurging out to sea."
- 是的 - 我就永远也写不出来
- Yeah. - I could never write that.
我也不行其实 那时布考斯基写的
Neither could I actually.I think it's Bukowski.
嘿 宝贝
Hey baby. [Chuckling]
- 看我给我们的宝贝女儿带什么了 - 操你妈!
- Look what I got for our favorite girl. - Motherfucker!
- 上帝啊! - 操你妈屎一样的骗子!
- Jesus Christ! - You fucking lying piece of shit!
你周六就结婚了? 那你给我说的那些屁话是什么意思?
You're getting married on Saturday?What's with all that shit you said to me?
- 斯蒂芬妮 别打了! - 我要给你解释!
- Stephanie stop! - [Jack] I can explain.!
- 你还说你爱我! - 是真的!
- [Sobbing] You said you loved me! - I do.!
- 去死吧! - 别打了 斯蒂芬妮!
- I hope you die! - Stop it Stephanie!
一幅猪相!你也是!
Fuckface! You too!
我?
Me?
- 你他妈的告诉玛雅了 是不是? - 没有 我没说
- You fucking told Maya didn't you? - No I did not.
没有 我没说
No I did not.
肯定是The Hitching Post的盖理
It must have been Garyat The Hitching Post.
我想我们第一天晚上就和他提过了
I think we mentioned it to himthe first night.
哦 是"我们"提的么? 是你提的 傻瓜!
Oh did we mention it?You mentioned it asshole!
我这儿真他妈的疼
I'm fucking hurting over here.
头抬高一点
Keep it elevated.
不 我什么都不要
[Elderly Woman] No I don't want anything.
呃 是我 迈尔斯
- [Answering Machine Beeps] - Uh it's Miles.
我必须得打电话 呃 再次告诉你…
I had to call and uh tell you again...
和你在一起我有多么愉快…
how much I enjoyedour time together...
还有 呃 我有多么难过…
and uh how sorry I am...
看着事情变成这样
that things turned outthe way they did.
我觉得你很了不起 玛雅
I think you're great Maya.
呃 我一直就这样认为 从第一次你 呃 在餐厅为我服务
Uh I always have from the first timethat you uh waited on me.
呃 既然我要坦白…
Uh and while I'm at it...
呃 我想也许你应该知道我的书…
uh I guess maybe youshould know that my book...
并没有出版
is not getting published.
我原以为这次 呃 可以成的 可是我又错了
I thought this one uh had a chance but I was wrong again.
又一次错了
Once again.
再见 呃…
So you see uh...
我其实并不是个作家
I'm not really much of a writer.
我什么都不是 真的
I am not much of anything really.
我可能得做手术了 没准儿得做两三个
I'm gonna have to have an operation maybe even a couple of'em.
他们要等我的鼻子先愈合了 再把它打开
They're gonna wait for my nose to heal first then they break it again.
哦 上帝幸好你还可以干旁白解说什么的
Oh Christ. Good thingyou have a voice - over career.
我连他妈那种也干不了了 我应该起诉她这个混蛋
It's gonna fuck that up too.I oughta sue her ass.
我不起诉的唯一原因就是为了保护克莉丝汀
The only reason I won'tis to protect Christine.
- 你可真替人着想 - 是啊
- That's thoughtful. - Yeah.
斯蒂芬妮怎么会知道是在星期六?
How did Stephanie knowit was on Saturday?
我们没有给盖理说这个吧
We didn't get into that with Gary.
呃 可能是… 呃 让我想想看
Huh. That's... Yeah let me think.
- 你肯定什么都没有对玛雅说? - 是的 我保证 我保证
- You sure you didn't say anything to Maya? - Yes I'm sure I'm sure.
你会让人怎么想 杰克?
And just what are you implying Jack?
我对你所作的一切非常生气 如果你想知道我的真实想法的话
I'm really pissed off at you about all this if you want to know the truth.
玛雅现在会对我怎么看 就因为我和你关系这么好?
What is Maya going to think of me now just for associating with you?
我不知道 肯定她觉得你很可疑
I don't know. Sure seems fishy.
是的
Well.
[TV:每当人们为饥饿的人作战…]
[TV:Man] Wherever there's a fightso hungry people can eat...
[我会在那里]
I'll be there.
[每当警察实施暴力…]
Wherever there's a copbeating up a guy...
[我会在那里…]
I'll be there.
[我会在疯狂尖叫的人们中]
I'll be in the way guys yellwhen they're mad.
你觉得看起来像什么?
What's this look like to you?
呃 我觉得像发生了严重的车祸
Uh it looks like you werein a bad car accident.
[TV:当人们吃着自己种养的…]
[TVContinues] When the peopleare eating the stuff they raised...
我饿了
I'm hungry.
来了
- [People Chattering] - [Woman] Here we go.
- 很好 - 谢谢
- Nice. - Thank you.
- 这是你的小餐巾 - 哦
- And here is your Handi Wipes. - Oh.
噢这是小餐巾啊 我差点以为你们在宣传性安全
So that's what those are. For a minuteI thought you were promoting safe sex.
这个笑话好 我要记住这个笑话
That's a good one.I'll have to remember that one.
- 我马上就给你拿玉米面包来 - 好的
- I'll be right back with your corn bread. - All righty.
我保证那个妞非常非常好玩
Bet you that chick's two tons of fun.
- 你知道 很舒适的那种? - 呒
- You know the grateful type? - Mm - mmm.
我不知道我也不想知道
I don't know.I wouldn't know about that.
呒
Mmm.
- 呒 - 来了
- Hmm. - Here you go.
技术很好…坎米
Nice technique there... Cammi.
谢谢 都是手腕功夫
Thank you. All in the wrist. [Giggles]
你知道 你看起来很眼熟
You know you look really familiar to me.
- 你住在这附近么? - 其实我们是从圣地亚哥来的怎么了?
- Are you from around here? - Actually we're from San Diego. Why?
我不知道我就是看着你眼熟
I don't know.You just seemed really familiar to me.
- 别介意 用餐吧 - 等一下 等一下
- Never mind. Enjoy your meal. - Hang on. Hang on.
呃 你知不知道德里克·索墨斯比?
Um did you ever knowa Derek Sommersby?
《一次人生》电视剧里的德里克·索墨斯比博士?
Dr. Derek Sommersbyfrom One Life To Live?
你想象一下他贴着邦迪 剪着短发
Just have to imagine himwith a bandage and shorter hair.
不会吧!
No way!
不会吧!哦 上帝!
No way! Oh my gosh!
太好了!哦 上帝啊!
[Squealing] That's great.! Oh my goodness.!
你能告诉我洗手间在哪里么?
Could you tell me wherethe bathroom is please?
噢 就在那过了那个野牛就是喔!
Oh yeah. It's right over there right past the buffalo. Wow!
噢 上帝啊 我简直不敢相信你坐在我的餐桌
Oh my gosh. I can't believeyou're sitting at my table.
听着 伙计 坎米一个小时后下班 所以我想…
Listen man Cammi gets offin an hour so I was thinking...
在这儿多点一会儿 喝点酒
I'd just hang around have a drink.
你知道 送她安全回家
- You know make sure she gets home safe. - [Laughs]
你在开玩笑吧 是不是?
You're joking right?
不是
No.
真他妈不敢相信
Un - fucking - believable.
我们能不能就回旅馆呆着…
Can't we just go back to the moteland hang out...
早上早点起 打打高尔夫…
get up early play nine holes of golf...
回家之前就这样?
before we head home?
听着 伙计 你是我的朋友…
Listen man you're my friend...
我知道你关心我
and I know you care about me.
我知道你反对 我尊重这些
I know you disapprove and I respect that.
但有些事我必须得做 你并不理解
But there are some things that I have to dothat you don't understand.
你了解文学 电影 葡萄酒…
You understand literature movies wine...
但你并不了解我的困境
but you don't understand my plight.
来了
Yeah? [Sighs]
- 天哪!上帝! - 靠 靠
- Holy shit!Jesus Christ! - Fuck. Fuck.
上帝 我他妈的在哪儿快冻僵了
God it's fucking freezing out there!
- 天哪 是 - 维柯丁呢 哪儿有 维柯丁?
- God yeah. - Vicodin. Where's the Vicodin?
呃…
Uh...
噢
Oh. [Panting]
给
Here.
噢 哦
Oh. Oh.
操他妈的那个妞已经结婚了
Fucking chick's married man.
什么?
What?
她老公上夜班 他回家在地板上抓住我们…
Her husband works the night shift and hecomes home and catches me on the floor...
我的小弟弟在她老婆屁股里
with my cock in his wife's ass.
噢 上帝 上帝 杰克!
Oh Jesus Christ.Jesus.Jack!
- 你一路从索尔万走回来的? - 不是 是跑回来的
- And you walked all the way from Solvang? - No ran.
脚腕也扭了
Twisted my ankle too.
- 那可有5公里啊 杰克 - 他妈的 对 有5公里
- That's five klicks Jack. - Fuckin' - A right it's five klicks.
有一段我还得穿过一个鸵鸟牧场
At one point I had to cutthrough an ostrich farm.
那些鸵鸟够狠
- Those fuckers are mean. - [Giggling]
呜!
Whoo!
- 哦 - 我们还得回去
- Oh.! [Laughing] - We gotta go back.
什么?
[Chuckles] What?
我们得回去 我把钱包落在那里了
We gotta go back. I left my wallet.
信用卡 现金 他妈的身份证
Credit cards cash my fucking I.D.
- 所有的东西我们得回去 - 很严重没关系
- Everything. We gotta go back. - Big deal. It's fine.
别担心 我们现在就打电话把你的卡都取消
Don't worry about it. We'll call nowand we'll cancel your cards.
不行 迈尔斯 你不明白我的结婚戒指
No Miles you don't understand.The wedding rings.
结婚戒指在我的钱包里
The wedding rings are in my wallet.
没关系 在你钱包里你把钱包丢在某个酒吧里了 行不行?
Fine they're in your wallet and youleft your wallet in some bar okay?
- 克莉丝汀 会理解的 - 她特别定制的两个戒指
- Christine will understand. - She had to order them special.
她花了很长很长时间才挑到的
It took her forever to find 'em.
那上面有海豚的设计 有梵语刻的名字
They've got this design of dolphinsand our names engraved in Sanskrit.
我们得回去 兄弟克莉丝汀 会把我钉死在十字架上 迈尔斯
We gotta go back man.Christine will fucking crucify me Miles.
不可能 不可能 不可能
No way no way no way.
求求你了 求求你了!
Please. Please!
算了吧 你的钱包在酒吧被偷了
Forget it.Your wallet was stolen in some bar.
我跟你说 那两个戒指是不可取代的
- It happens every day. - No we gotta go back and get my wallet Miles.
- 这种事情每天都有 - 不行 我们必须得回去把钱包拿回来 迈尔斯
I'm telling you those rings are irreplaceable.
看 我知道我自己有多糟 好么? 我知道把事情搞砸了
Look I know I fucked up okay?I know I fucked up.
- 但你得帮帮我 - 是的
- But you've gotta help me. - Yeah.
你必须得帮我 迈尔斯 求你了 求你了!
You've gotta help me Miles please.! Please.!
我不能失去克莉丝汀 迈尔斯
I can't lose Christine Miles.
我真的…不能我不能失去克莉丝汀
I just... I can't.I can't lose Christine.
- 呒呒 - 我知道我搞砸了
- Mm - hmm. - I know I fucked up.
我知道我干了坏事 行不行? 我知道我是个坏蛋
I know I did a bad thing all right?And I know I'm a bad person.
我知道我是 但是你得帮我 你必须得帮我 迈尔斯
I know I am. But you gotta help me!You have to help me Miles.
好不好? 告诉我你会帮我的
Okay? Tell me you'll help me.
如果我失去了克莉丝汀 我 - 我…
If I lose Christine I - I - I...
我什么都不是了
I'm nothing.
我真的 - 我什么都不是了
I just have... I'm nothing.
天哪
[Sobbing] God.
- 她有没有告诉你她结婚了? - 说了
- [Miles] Did she tell you she was married? - Yeah.
那你她妈的是怎么想的?
So what the fuck were you thinking?
他本来说是6：00回来的结果5：00就滚回来了
Wasn't supposed to be back till 6:00.Fucker rolls in at 5:00.
卡时间卡得有点紧 你不觉得么?
[Miles] Cutting it a little close don't you think?
- 就是这片 - 你确定?
- This is the block. - You sure?
是的
Yeah.
就是这个 就是这个
That's it. That's it.
绝对是这个
That's the one right there.
- 是么? - 是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
好的
Okay.
好了那 你打算怎么办?
All right.Okay so what's the plan?
呃 我打算…
Uh the plan is...
你去
you go.
- 我? - 因为我的脚腕
- Me? - 'Cause of my ankle.
还很疼你去解释一下情况 迈尔斯
Still hurts.Just go explainthe situation Miles.
解释情况是么
[Laughs] Explain the situation. Yes.
"对不起 先生我的朋友就是两个小时前操你老婆的那个
"Excuse me sir. My friend was the oneballing your wife a couple of hours ago.
"很抱歉 他好像把钱包落在这儿了
"Really sorry. He seems tohave left his wallet behind.
"我想我能不能进去四处找找 我不知道"
I was wondering if I could come inand just poke around. I don't know."
- 对 就像那样 挺不错的 - 哦 看在上帝的份儿上
- Yeah just like that. That's good. - Oh for Christ's sake.
哦 去他妈的!我去什么事都得我做
Oh fuck it! I'll go.I guess I have to do everything.
别等一下
No. Hold on.
你以为我不会操你么 婊子? 我现在就操你
[Man] You think I don't fuck you bitch?I'm fucking you now.
我是个坏女人我是个坏女人
I'm a bad girl. I'm a bad girl.!
你把他捡回来操他 是不是 婊子?
You picked him up and you fucked him didn't you bitch?
是的 我把他捡回来操他我是个坏女人
Yeah I picked him up and I fucked him.I'm a bad girl.!
你喜欢操他 是不是 你这个妓女?
You liked fucking him didn't you you little whore?
我就喜欢你抓住我操他!啊!啊!
I liked it when you caught me fucking him!Oh yes! Oh yeah!
你这个臭婊子
You are a bad bitch.
- 对 你抓住我 - 你这个妓女
- Yeah you caught me. - You're such a whore.
哦 对!
Oh yeah.!
- 哦 宝贝 - 哦 真好!
- Oh baby. - Oh it's so good.!
我操了他
[Cammi] I fucked him.
- 你够坏 - 是的 是的
- [Man] You're so bad. - I am. Yeah.
你这个妓女
[Groaning] You are such a whore.
- 他妈的怎么了? - 钱包!他把德里克的钱包拿走了!
- What the fuck.! - The wallet.! He's got Derek's wallet.!
[收音机：我想他们对抗议的严重程度感到震惊]
[Radio:Man] I think theywere surprised by the level of protest...
[这些事情居然真的在公司发生了]
that was really happeningwithin the company.
[他们要讨回公道 他们说我们不能就这样算了…]
The injustice may be their plan and they said "Well we can'tjust go..."
- 哦 给你的钱包!哦 妈的! - 操你妈的!
- Oh! Here's your wallet! Oh shit! - Motherfucker!
他妈的开门
- [Grunting] - Open the goddamn door!
- 我要杀了你 傻瓜! - 你拿到了!你拿到我的钱包了!
- I'm gonna kill your ass.! - You got it.! You got my wallet.!
我会找到你的!我会找到你的 小家伙!我会找到你这个傻瓜的!
I'll find you! I will find you bub!I'll find your ass!
你逃不了的 你逃不了!
You're mine man! You're mine!
操你妈的!我会抓住你的!
Fuck you.! I'm gonna get your ass.!
- 你想让我开么? - 不用 这样很好我来开
- You wanna let me drive? - No it's all right. I got it.
嘿 你知道 你应该请玛雅一起去婚礼
Hey you know you oughtainvite Maya to the wedding.
呒
Hmm.
我觉得请玛雅去婚礼…
Somehow I thinkinviting Maya to the wedding...
在这个节骨眼上不合适
is not the right moveat this juncture.
我不知道
I don't know.
其实 在你那些骗剧之后…
In fact after all of your shenanigans...
我觉得再去The Hitching Post都困难
it's gonna be hard for meto ever go to The Hitching Post again.
你知道 应该有个好点的方式回答我
You know there was a nice wayto respond to that.
- 来吧 让我来开 - 不 我来开你应该休息
- Come on. Let me drive. - No I got it. You should rest.
你猜怎么着? 我很想开
You know what? I feel like driving.
好吧
Okay.
呃…嘿 把安全带系好 好么?
Uh... hey put on your seat belt okay?
我正要系呢 有什么问题么?
I was just about to.What's the problem?
- 只想提醒你注意安全 - 我们错过入口了
- Just want to remind you to be safe. - We missed the entrance.
你要干什么 杰克? 嘿 嘿 嘿 嘿!
What are you doing Jack?Hey hey hey hey!
- 喔 喔 你到底要干什么? - 等一下
- Whoa whoa whoa! What the hell are you doing? - Hang on.
杰克!
Jack!
他妈的怎么搞得?
What the fuck!
- 你说的看起来像出了交通事故 - 他妈的!
- You said it looked like an accident. - What the fuck!
我会出钱的
I'll pay for it.
上帝啊 杰克!哦 你看看这儿!
Jesus. Christ Jack!Oh for Ch... Look at this!
- 嗯 - 哦
- Huh. - Oh.
不知道
I don't know.
好像这样车里的人不会受伤
Doesn't look like anyonewas injured in this one.
不会吧 不
No. No.
- 注意你的头 - 好的
- Watch your head. - Yeah.
天哪 你弄断了好几处 你知道么
Boy you broke a couple of'em you know.
- 随便 对不起 - 不行 不行 不行这个不能"随便"
- Whatever. Sorry. - No no no. It's not "whatever."
你他妈的废物
You fuckin' derelict.
准备好了么?
You ready?
一不做二不休
Just get it over with.
好了 好了
Okeydoke. All right.
嗯 我想就这样了
Well I guess that's about it.
- 想进去么? - 哦 不了不了 全靠你自己了
- Want to come inside? - Uh no. No you're on your own.
好吧 我想晚餐预演的时候再见
All right. I guessI'll see you at the rehearsal.
是的
Yup.
我爱你 兄弟
- [Laughing] - I love you man.
是的我也爱你
Yeah. Back at ya.
- 迈尔斯 等他们看到你的车再开走 - 我知道 我知道 我知道
- Miles don't drive away until they see the car. - I know I know I know.
嘿 等一下 等一下为什么我没有受伤?
Hey wait a second. Wait a second.How come I wasn't hurt?
因为你系安全带了
'Cause you were wearing your seat belt.
没破绽了
Nicely done.
- 嗨 - 杰克
- Hi. - Jack.
- 是的 - 呃 克莉丝汀·迈克!
- Yeah. - Uh Christine Mike!
阿门
Amen.
嘿 迈尔斯
Hey Miles.
嗨 维姬 喔 你真美
Hi Vicki.Wow you look beautiful.
谢谢
Thanks.
嗯 这是 肯·科特兰 我丈夫
Um this is Ken Cortland my husband.
- 你好 - 你好
- How are you? - How are you?
- 很好 谢谢 - 是的 是的很高兴见到你
- Good thanks. - Yeah yeah. Nice to meet you.
- 你很幸运 - 是的 我是的谢谢
- You're a lucky guy. - Yes I am. Thank you.
嗯
Yeah.
那 我在车里等你了
Well I'll just wait for you at the car.
- 很高兴见到你 迈尔斯 - 肯
- It was great meeting you Miles. - Ken.
- 嗯 他可真大度 - 是啊 他这方面很好
- Well that was big of him. - Yeah he's good that way.
- 他很替人着想 - 那很好
- He's very considerate. - That's great.
你怎么样了?
So how are you doing?
可能好些了 也可能更糟了
Since the last time we spoke?I don't know.
你怎么样了?
Could be better. Could be worse.
- 那你的书怎么样了? - 呒 很不幸被拒了
- So what's happening with your book? - Um universally rejected.
- 事不过三 - 哦 迈尔斯 太糟糕了
- Strike three. - Oh Miles that's awful.
你打算怎么办?
What are you gonna do?
回到讲台上 我想 或者不
Back to the drawing board I guess. Or not.
我不知道
I don't know.
嗯 不管怎样 你结婚了
So anyway you're married.
恭喜 你看上去很幸福
Congratulations. You look happy.
- 我是幸福的 - 很好
- I am. - Good.
看起来每个人都结婚了
Seems like everybody's getting married.
去年都是离婚的 今年都是结婚的
Last year was all divorces.This year it's all weddings.
- 周期性的 我想 - 是的
- Cyclical I guess. - I guess.
嗯 我们一起参加招待会怎么样?
Well uh what do you saywe hit the reception?
喝点香槟 给新人们祝词 嗯?
Have some champagne toast the newlyweds huh?
我不行 我不喝酒了
Not me. I'm not drinking.
你诫酒了 真的?
You quit drinking. Really?
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
明白了
I see.
嗯 明白了 很好
Yes I see. Great.
那 再次恭喜你 维姬
Well congratulations again Vicki.
天哪 这可是个好消息
Boy that's wonderful news.
- 那边见 迈尔斯? - 好的
- See you over there Miles? - Yeah.
嗯
Hmm.
"他的骨髓 "我漫无目的的重复着
[Boy] "'The marrow ofhis bone 'I repeated aimlessly.
这 至少 穿透了我的心灵
"This at last penetrated my mind.
菲尼亚斯已经死了 从他的骨髓中
"Phineas had diedfrom the marrow of his bone...
鲜血流向他的心脏
"flowing down his bloodstreamto his heart.
我并没有哭 也没有为芬尼哭
"I did not cry then or ever about Finny.
我甚至在葬礼上都没有哭 站在那里…
"I did not cry even when I stood...
看着他被放进他家波士顿外…
"watching him being lowered intohis family's straitlaced burial ground...
刻板的家庭墓地里
"outside of Boston.
我无法逃脱这种感觉 好像这是我自己的葬礼…
"I could not escape the feelingthat this was my own funeral...
而你是不会在自己的葬礼上哭的
and you do not cry in that case. "
我要不要继续读下一章? 雷蒙德先生?
Should I keep readingthe next chapter Mr. Raymond?
呃 不用 不用我们下周一再继续
Uh no no.We'll pick up there Monday.
您有一条留言
[Male Voice Electronic] One new message.
你好 迈尔斯 是 玛雅
[Maya] Hello Miles. It's Maya.
谢谢你的信
Thanks for your letter.
我 - 我应该早点打电话…
I - I would have called sooner...
但我需要些时间想一想已经发生的一切…
but I think I needed some time to thinkabout everything that happened...
还有你写给我的东西
and what you wrote to me.
还有一个原因 呃 我没有早点打…
Another reason um I didn't call you sooner...
是因为我想读完你的小说 我昨晚终于读完了
is because I wanted to finish your book which I finally did last night.
我真的认为很棒 迈尔斯
And I think it's really lovely Miles.
你用词很娴熟
You're so good with words.
谁在乎到底有没有被出版啊?
Who caresif it's not getting published?
里面有很多很美…很伤感的东西
There are so many beautifuland... painful things about it.
你真的都经历过么?
Did you really go through all that?
一定很痛苦
Must have been awful.
还有姐姐那个人物…天哪 真是落魄
And the sister character...geez what a wreck.
但是我得说 嗯 结尾让人很迷惑
But I have to say that well I was really confused by the ending.
我的意思是 那个父亲到底是自杀了还是怎么回事?
I mean did the fatherfinally commit suicide or what?
都让我想疯了
It's driving me crazy.
反正…
Anyway...
这里最近变冷了 经常下雨…
it's turned cold and rainy here lately...
但是我喜欢冬天
but I like winter.
嗯 听着 如果你还想过来的话 你应该告诉我一声
So listen if you ever do decide to comeup here again you should let me know.
我是说去我们餐厅 不过说实话…
I would say stop by the restaurant but to tell you the truth...
我也不知道我还会在那里工作多久…
I'm not sure how much longerI'm gonna be working there...
因为我快毕业了
because I'm going to graduate soon.
所以可能我会换个地方
So I'll probably want to relocate.
我是说 再看吧
I mean we'll see.
反正 就像我说的 我真的很喜欢的你的小说
Anyway like I said I really loved your novel.
别放弃 迈尔斯 继续写下去
Don't give up Miles.Keep writing.
希望你一切都好
I hope you're well.
再见
Bye.